http://subscene.com/u/659433
Improved by: @Ivandrofly
(MUSIC)
FLINT: Have you ever felt like
you were a little bit different?
Like you had something
unique to offer the world,
if you could just get
people to see it.
Then you know
exactly how it felt
to be me.
TEACHER: Go ahead, Flint.
(FLINT CLEARS THROAT)
What is the number one problem
facing our community today?
Untied shoelaces.
(ALL CHATTERING)
Which is why I've invented a
laceless alternative foot covering.
Spray-On Shoes.
- Voilà.
- GIRL: They're so nifty.
How you gonna get
them off, nerd?
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
What a freak. He wants to
be smart, but that's lame.
(BELL RINGS)
Oh.
(CRYING)
FLINT: I wanted to
run away that day.
But you can't run away
from your own feet.
(GRUNTING)
Ah!
Nah. Not every sardine
is meant to swim, son.
I don't understand
fishing metaphors.
- DAD: What did I say?
- MOM: Don't worry.
(FLINT SOBBING)
Honey, I think your
shoes are wonderful.
Everyone just thinks
I'm a weirdo.
So?
People probably thought that
these guys were weirdoes too.
But that never stopped them.
I was saving this for
your birthday, but here.
A professional-grade lab coat.
Just like the real guys wear.
(CHUCKLES)
It fits perfect.
The world needs your
originality, Flint.
You just have to grow into it.
And I know that you're gonna
do big things someday.
(MUSIC)
From that moment on,
FLINT: I was determined to
invent something great.
Remote Control Television.
TV ANNOUNCER: And,
the pitch is in.
- FLINT: Eventually.
- BOY: Ow, ow, ow.
Hair Un-Balder.
(BOTH SCREAM)
FLINT: Flying Car.
Monkey Thought Translator.
VOICE: Hungry. Hungry.
Hungry. How wise.
No, Steve. No, no, no, no, no!
No, please! Leave it...
TIM: Ah! Ratbirds.
Hey, what's going on, little guy?
Ah!
EARL: Flint Lockwood.
FLINT: My dream was
to help my hometown,
a tiny island hidden under
the "A " in "Atlantic"
called Swallow Falls.
We were famous for sardines,
until the day the Baby Brent
Sardine Cannery closed for good.
Right after everyone in the
world realized that sardines
are super gross.
Soon, all of us were stuck eating the
sardines that no one else wanted.
Poached, fried, boiled,
dried, candied
and juiced. Ugh.
Life became gray and flavorless.
But when all seemed lost,
I stared at defeat,
and found hope.
(MUSIC)
My name is Flint Lockwood.
And I was about to
invent a machine
that turns water
into food.
Steve, my best friend
and trusted colleague.
(OVER SPEAKER)
Steve.
Can I count on your help?
Can.
I knew I could.
Button, on. Memory, activate.
Blueprints, awesome.
Begin nano-mutation.
Radiation matrix, secure.
Computer, boot.
Coolness enhancement, complete.
Engage coffee break.
(ELEVATOR MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
Networking power grid.
Beginning conversion of water
into food.
Hydrating protein matrix.
Calibrating flavor panel.
Priming chow plopper.
Uploading cool machine voice.
COMPUTER: Cheeseburger.
Everyone is going to love this.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
FLINT: Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Ah!
Flint!
FLINT: Sorry, Dad.
Steve, keep working.
(FLINT HUMMING ACTION MOVIE THEME)
Scanning hand.
Twaap!
(HUMMING)
(IMITATES BEEPING NOISES)
Whoosh!
(FLINT HUMMING)
That's a really weird dude.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(HUMMING)
Re-energizing tower unit.
(MAKES MECHANICAL SOUNDS)
(SCREAMS)
Jeez. See you, Dad.
(IMITATES DOOR SLIDING SOUND)
Flint. Um...
Um...
Don't you think it's time to give up
this inventing thing, get a real job?
No, why?
Well, all your technology stuff,
it just ends in disaster.
The ratbirds, yes, they escaped
and bred at a surprising rate.
But I took care of that
problem and disposed of them.
(BILLY SCREAMS)
CAL: Billy, just play dead.
Flint, you don't keep throwing your
net where there aren't any fish.
What? I want you
to work full-time
at the tackle shop. The tackle shop?
Oh, Dad, no.
Tackle is a good career.
Please, I'm so close
with this one.
I just have to hook it up to the power
station and give it power and it'll work.
And... And then you could
sell food in the shop,
and then everyone won't have
to eat sardines anymore.
It is going to be so awesome.
I'm sorry, son.
STEVE: Ouch. No more inventing.
Dad, I know I can do this.
And Mom did too.
(SIGHS)
FLINT: It had been almost
10 years since Mom died,
and Dad still didn't
understand me like she did.
Come on. Let's open the shop.
Tim and Son Sardine
Bait and Tackle.
You feeling it?
Mm-hm.
KIDS ON TV: Look
out, Baby Brent!
Uh-oh.
MALE ANNOUNCER ON TV:
Baby Brent Sardines.
FEMALE ANNOUNCER: Hand-packed
in Swallow Falls.
As your mayor, I know it's time to put
our sardine-canning past behind us
and look to the future.
Sardine tourism!
That's why, without
consulting anyone,
I spent the entire town budget on
the thing that is under this tarp,
which I will be unveiling today.
(VOICE ECHOING)
at noon.
Featuring a live appearance
by Baby Brent himself.
BRENT: What is up, everybody?
Hey. Hey, it's Baby Brent.
What you doing? Stacking cans
with me on them as a baby?
Uh-oh. Ha-ha-ha.
(LAUGHING)
Anyways, who wants to
watch me cut the ribbon
at the mayor's unveiling thing?
I'll be using these bad
boys to help save the town.
Boo-yow! Ha-ha.
All right, you guys.
Sardines, yeah.
Swallow Falls forever!
Oh. What a delight.
Listen, you, uh... Maybe you
wanna go to that unveiling?
You know, Dad, why don't you go ahead.
I'll, uh...
I'll hold down the fort here.
Really? You sure
you can handle it?
Heh-heh-heh. Yeah, Dad, I'm
pretty sure I'll be fine.
Ha. All right, then.
I'll be back in half
an hour, skipper.
Okay. Bye.
(HUMMING)
This hellhole is too
small for me, Brent.
I wanna be big.
I want people to look at me and
say, "That is one big mayor."
And that's why this has to work.
It has to work.
Otherwise, I'm just a tiny
mayor of a tiny town,
full of tiny sardine-sucking
knuckle-scrapers.
But not me, right?
Oh, not you, Brent. No.
You've always been like a son to me.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(APPLAUSE)
He-hey, everybody.
Under this tarp is the greatest tourist
attraction ever built by humans.
We just need 17,000
more gigajoules.
MAYOR: An attraction so...
Go, go, go.
(MUSIC)
What are you doing, Flint Lockwood?
Wha...! Oh!
Just, uh, holding my hands, uh,
behind my back respectfully, sir.
You know what you
are, Flint Lockwood?
No. A shenaniganizer.
A tomfool.
You see my beautiful angel son Cal?
What's up?
I love him so much.
This is my only son.
I want him to have
a bright future.
A future in which you
don't ruin our town's day
with one of your crazy science
doodly-bopper thingies.
Well, that's all behind me...
You see this contact
lens, Flint Lockwood?
Mm-hm. This contact
lens represent you.
All right. And my eye
represents my eye.
Okay. I got my eye on you.
Oh, my gosh, a jaywalker. Hey.
And I've arranged for live
coverage from a major network
and their most experienced
professional reporter.
WOMAN: Oh, just send the intern.
She's cute and she's super perky.
Well, those are the only things we
look for in a TV weatherperson.
Intern. How would you like to do a
weather report from a rinky-dink island
in the middle of the ocean
as a favor to my cousin?
Really?
Can you believe it, Manny?
Temporary professional
meteorologist.
Whoo! Okay, Manny,
what about this?
Welcome, America,
I'm Sam Sparks.
Hello, America, Sam Sparks here.
America, hi. I didn't
see you there.
It's me, Sam Sparks.
On my way across the ocean.
MAYOR: Now, when she gets here, I
wanna see a lot of smiling faces.
Act like, "Hey, whoa."
FLINT: This is a great idea.
MALE ANNOUNCER ON TV:
Weather News Network.
Weather news happens,
or not.
Now we're over to Swallow Falls,
where our intern is on her
first day on the job.
Or should I say, first
gray on the job.
Looks pretty cloudy
there, intern.
Hello, Sam Sparks, I'm America.
It's Swallow Falls degrees and, uh...
Well, let's just go to the mayor.
Thank you and welcome,
national television audience.
You are about to witness an
historic event, undoubtedly...
(SCREAMING)
And now, here to cut
the ceremonial ribbon.
Swallow Falls' favorite
son, Baby Brent!
He's still got it, folks.
Yeah.
(ALL CHEER)
I'm the best person
in the whole town.
Uh-oh.
(MUSIC)
Oh! Food synthesis, go.
(LAUGHS)
My chest hairs are tingling.
Something's wrong.
(GRUNTS)
Well, here it is. The attraction the
whole world has been waiting for:
Sardine Land.
(CROWD CHEERING)
With rides and exhibits.
And featuring Shamo, the
world's largest sardine
and his flaming hoop of glory.
Those of you in the
splash zone, look out.
MAN: Yeah!
(YELLS THEN GASPS)
MACHINE: Cheeseburger.
EARL: Flint Lockwood.
Just a second. I'm in
the middle of a...
Ah! Ah!
(SCREAMING)
Well, looks like things in Swallow Falls
are sardine to get better. For...
(MUMBLING) Whatjust
happened to me?
Ah! Sorry.
(FLINT SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
Oh!
No.
Ah! You're under arrest,
Flint Lockwood.
Thank goodness you only caused
minimal damage to Sardine Land.
(ALL GASP)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Aw, come on.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
BRENT: I really shouldn't
be running with these.
STEVE: Jump, jump, jump,
run, run, jump, jump, run.
Yippee!
(SPEAKS IN SPANISH)
(MUFFLED SHOUTING)
- MAN: It's a good thing no one got hurt!
- EARL: Flint Lockwood!
WOMAN: I didn't get hurt, but that does
not mean that I'm not still mad at you.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(MUSIC)
(GLASS CRACKING)
(CROWD GASPS)
(MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
FLINT: Ah!
Oh, my gosh. I am so sorry.
Are you okay?
I didn't get a chance to...
It's okay, it's just pain.
Sorry, I'm not myself today.
My whole career was ruined by some
crazy jerk riding a homemade rocket.
Wait a minute.
What is going on with your feet?
Spray-On Shoes. They,
uh, don't come off.
Cool. Ah!
This could solve the
untied shoes epidemic.
What are they made of, some kind
of elastic biopolymer adhesive?
Yeah.
Exactly.
I mean... Heh-heh-heh.
Wow, they're shiny. I'm Sam.
Flint. Steve.
Is that a Monkey
Thought Translator?
- Steve.
- SAM: Hah!
Incredible. Did you
make all of this stuff?
You hit me with a rocket.
You kicked me in the face.
I said I was sorry. Oh!
Do you know how hard it is to
break into the weather game?
I spent my entire life
building up to that moment.
You get one shot at the show.
SAM: And if you don't make it,
it's back to cleaning
the barometers.
Cheese?
(SNARLS)
Oh!
(RATBIRD SQUAWKS)
But that could only mean...
(GASPS)
(ALL GASP)
(SQUAWKS)
(GASPING)
STEVE: Excited. Excited.
(LAUGHS)
My machine works.
It really works! Ha-ha-ha.
Your machine?
Is that what that rocket was?
Uh... Do you like it?
I love it!
(MUMBLING) This is just amazing.
Look at this.
This is the greatest weather
phenomenon in history.
Hey, aren't you a weathergirl?
(GASPS)
SAM: Manny, get your camera.
KIDS: Whoa.
THIS JUST IN: Our humiliated weather
intern is apparently back for more.
Thanks, Patrick. Okay, everybody,
you are not gonna believe this one,
but I am standing in the
middle of a burger rain.
You may have seen
a meteor shower
but you've never seen a
shower meatier than this.
For a town stuck eating sardines,
this is totally manna from heaven.
JOE: This tastes significantly
better than sardines.
(CROWD CLAPPING AND CHATTERING)
Mm-mm-mm.
This is going to be big.
SAM ON TV: This food weather
was created intentionally
by meek-ish backyard
tinkerer Flint Lockwood.
ALL: Huh?
Flint Lockwood?
Hi. Ah!
You're under arrest for
ruining Sardine Land.
SAM: Flint, those
burgers were awesome.
The producer called and he was like,
"Everybody loves that food weather."
Food weather. What?
This could be even bigger
than Sardine Land.
- Can you make it rain food again?
- EARL: No...
I don't know if I...
You're gonna do it again?
You gotta be kidding.
Please, please, please.
Yes. No.
Dad, just give me one more chance.
We both know this was an accident.
I know.
Cheeseburgers from the sky
that's not natural.
My invention could
save the whole town.
You will be so proud of me, Dad.
Plus,
(WHISPERS)
there's a girl here.
(SIGHS)
Can you look me in the eye and tell
me you've got this under control
and it's not gonna end
up in a disaster?
(WEAKLY)
Yes.
Mm.
(FLINT WHIMPERING)
(WHIMPERING)
I've got this under control and
it's not gonna end in disaster. Oh.
(SIGHS THEN COUGHS)
All right. Thanks, Dad.
Oh, sure. Okay. So, Sam,
this is where the magic happens.
Lick. Lick. Lick.
(MUSIC)
COMPUTER: Welcome, Flint.
Wow. You seriously spend
a lot of time alone.
What? Ha-ha-ha.
So here's how it works.
Water goes in the top, and
food comes out the bottom.
When you shot it into
the stratosphere,
you figured it would induce
a molecular phase change
of the vapor from the
cumulonimbus layer?
That's actually a really
smart observation.
I mean...
(GIGGLES)
The clouds probably
have water in them,
which, uh, I guess, is why you shot
it up there in the first place.
Right, right. That's why I...
I did that.
On purpose. Right. Yeah.
Right. Of course.
(BOTH CHUCKLE NERVOUSLY)
Okay.
The machine uses a principle
of hydro-genetic mutation.
Water molecules are bombarded
with microwave radiation,
which mutates their genetic recipe
into any kind of food you want.
So...
Pizza? Yes.
Mashed potatoes?
Yes.
Peas?
Yes, that's also a food.
Steak? Apples?
Yes. Mm-hm.
Apple sauce?
BLT? Yes.
I'm pretty sure I said any kind of food.
Chicken wings?
Okay. But just think about what you're
saying and if it's a food, then yes.
Baloney. Baloney.
That is a food.
How about Jell-O?
Do you like Jell-O?
I love Jell-O.
I love Jell-O too. Oh, and
peanut butter, right?
Oh, no, no, no, I am severely
allergic to peanuts.
Hey, me too.
So what's it called?
Peanut allergy.
No, the machine. Of course.
It's called the Flint Lockwood
Diatonic Super-Mutating.
Dynamic Food Replicator.
Or, for short:
The FLDSMDFR.
Fliminadifiser?
FLDSMDFR.
Fliminubahdibferer?
Fli.
Suh.
Fdiferf.
Oh. Manny, make
sure you get this.
He's gonna make the food now.
Uh...
Now?
Well, um, the thing is, I can't
wait to show you this
hilarious Internet video.
(MUSIC PLAYS ON MONITOR)
SAM: What?
CAT ON MONITOR: Fight the power!
SAM: What is this?
(SAM LAUGHS)
It's so cute.
FLINT: Pushing. Folding.
Connecting.
Taping. Turning. Painting.
Switching.
Staring.
Motivating.
Placing button.
I can't believe I've
been watching this
for three hours. I know. Ha-ha.
FLINT: It's working.
What do you guys
want for breakfast?
Gummi Bears. Whoa, Steve, no.
We both know how you get
around Gummi Bears.
How about
eggs. And toast.
Orange juice. And.
BOTH: Bacon.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
To the computer.
(TYPING)
SAM: So you're
sure this is safe?
Heh-heh. Don't worry. I have a
Dangeometer that lets us know
if the food is going
to over-mutate.
SAM: What happens if
the food over-mutates?
FLINT: I don't know.
But that'll never happen.
All right, this
probably won't explode.
What?
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
MACHINE: Bacon.
Well, those cheeseburgers
were only the beginning
because a breakfast system is
on its way to Swallow Falls.
My forecast?
Sunny side up.
(LESLEY GORE'S "SUNSHINE
AND LOLLIPOPS" PLAYING)
Yeah. Yeah.
(SQUAWKING)
(GRUNTING)
Flint, my boy. Can you do lunch?
All right, here's the skinny:
You keep making it
rain the snackadoos,
weathergirl provides
free advertising,
I have taken out a very
high-interest loan
to convert this Podunk town
into a tourist food-topia.
All you have to do is make it
rain food three meals a day,
every day for the
foreseeable future,
and in 30 days we hold a grand
reopening of the island
as a must-see
cruise destination.
And everyone, everywhere,
is going to love your invention.
Do you think so?
I know so.
(LESLEY GORE'S "SUNSHINE
AND LOLLIPOPS" PLAYING)
Now that's what I call
poultry in motion.
Mr. Lockwood, may I
please have waffles?
Falafels?
Jellybeans.
Avocado. Coming right up.
Leftovers?
Not a problem with Flint Lockwood's
latest invention, the Outtasighter,
so-named because it catapults
uneaten food out of sight,
and therefore, out of mind.
Huh?
KIDS: Jellybeans!
Awesome.
- BLT.
- MAN 1: Doughnuts.
Pie.
Gummi bears.
- Fish.
- MAN 2: Creme brulee!
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
A pizza stuffed inside a Turkey,
the whole thing deep-fried
and dipped in chocolate.
It's me, the mayor. Oh. Uh...
You look different. Uh...
Did you get a new haircut?
Yes, I did.
Thank you for noticing.
(LESLEY GORE'S "SUNSHINE
AND LOLLIPOPS" PLAYING)
(MACHINE TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
- I love you, kid.
- BOY 1: Thanks, Dad. I love you.
BOY 2: I love spending
time with you, Dad.
Hey, Dad, I'm headed
back to the lab.
If you wanna come, I could
show you how I make the food.
Uh... No, thanks.
That techno-food, it's... It's too
complicated for an old fisherman.
Got it.
Could still use your help
around here, though, you know.
I'm working with the
mayor now, Dad.
I mean, the town's grand
reopening is in, like, a week.
Right. Got it.
(BELL JINGLES)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Flint Lockwood?
FLINT: Yeah?
Uh...
It's my son Cal's
birthday tomorrow,
and I was just wondering if you could
make it rain something special.
Well, I'm pretty
backed up on requests.
Plus, you're always mean to me.
It'll be just one time,
for my special
angel's special day.
Uh... I don't know.
You know, I don't wanna
overwork the machine, so...
Okay. I knew it was a long shot.
I just wanted Cal to see how
much his father loves him.
I thought you would understand.
You know how fathers
always trying to express
their love and appreciation
for their sons.
Earl, wait.
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
Whew.
Touch. Touch. Touch.
I've got an idea.
(SQUAWKS)
(MUSIC)
Whoa.
Happy Birthday, son.
Dad?
This is your day. Go have fun.
- I love you guys. You're awesome.
- EARL: I love you too, son.
- CAL: Whoo!
- REGINA: Have a good time, baby.
KIDS: Ice cream!
Yeah! Cool.
BOY: Strawberry's my favorite.
(KIDS LAUGHING)
(KIDS SCREAMING)
CAL: Come on, Dad.
I don't know, Cal.
This doesn't look safe!
(SCREAMS)
(BOTH LAUGH)
I love you, son.
I know, Dad.
You tell me every day.
(BOY LAUGHING)
Flint, this is amazing.
And designing the ice cream
to accumulate into scoops,
I don't know how
you're gonna top this.
Maybe with hot fudge.
(LAUGHS)
CAL: Hey, Flint.
You wanna be in a
snowball fight with us?
Flint, what's the problem?
I've never actually been
in a snowball fight.
Really? I don't even
know the rules.
Is there like a point
system or is it
to the death?
No... Ah...
You've nev...? I mean, look, even Steve
is throwing chocolate snowballs.
(GIBBERING)
Oh. Eh.
So like this?
(GRUNTS)
No, harder than that.
(MUSIC)
Oh. Snowball! Snowball,
snowball, snowball!
Snowball. Snowball.
Well, something to be
said for enthusiasm.
Snowball!
(LAUGHS)
Snowball and snowball.
WOMAN: Kids?
What's going on?
Snowball. Ha-ha-ha.
(KIDS LAUGHING)
- BOY: Snowball.
- GIRL: Snowball. Snowball.
SAM ON TV: I
scream, you scream,
we all scream for Flint Lockwood's
latest tasty town-wide treat,
with flurries of frozen fun on
what the mayor declared to be
an ice cream snow day.
He'd also like to invite everyone in
the world to catch a cruise liner
and come on down this Saturday
for the grand opening
of Chew And Swallow,
a town that is truly à la mode.
(WOMAN 1 SPEAKS IN FRENCH OVER TV)
(WOMAN 2 SPEAKS IN ARABIC OVER TV)
WOMAN 3 IN BRITISH ACCENT: A town
that is truly topped with ice cream.
With today's scoop for the
Weather News Network,
I'm Sam Sparks.
CAL: Flint, this is the
best breakfast ever!
That's it!
Researching. Role-playing.
Dialing. Waiting.
(PHONE RINGING)
Sam Sparks. Hanging up.
Regretting. Re-psyching.
Saying what I'm doing.
Flint? "Hi, Sam, how are you?
That's nice."
I was wondering if you would
like to go on a da..."
Activity with me tomorrow.
Um... Okay.
Great, bye.
Meet me in the forest.
Nailed it. Gotta go, Steve.
Keep an eye on the lab for me.
(GUAGE CLICKING)
Steve.
ANNOUNCER OVER TV:
Foster still at the plate.
And nobody out.
SAM: Where are we going?
FLINT: Oh, nowhere.
I just thought it'd be nice
for the two of us to
go on a walk together.
(CHUCKLES)
Like you do as friends. Uh...
Oh, my, what's that?
Wow.
(MUSIC)
Oh. Jell-O's my favorite.
You never made a request, so
I made one for you.
Flint?
FLINT: Join me.
Whoa!
(GASPS)
Oh! Oh! Oh!
(GRUNTS)
But, uh... Uh, how did you...?
I made it rain Jell-O in
the middle of the night,
then I gathered it up
with the Outtasighter
before anyone woke up and then I
brought it here and pressed it
into a gigantic custom-carved plastic
Tupperware mold I made. No big deal.
(PIANO PLAYING)
Everything's made of Jell-O.
This piano, those sconces,
that ghetto blaster, that
Jell-O, that aquarium,
that Venus de Milo
with your face on it
next to a Michelangelo's David
that also has your face.
Come on, Sam, what
are you waiting for?
Nothing!
(LAUGHS)
Whoo! Yeah.
(LAUGHING)
SAM: Hee-hee. Boing,
boing, boing, whoo!
Whoo!
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH LAUGH)
Cannonball!
Belly flop.
(MUMBLING)
Why did I do that?
(MUSIC)
So Jell-O. Right. Right, right.
It's a solid, it's a liquid,
it's a visco-elastic polymer made of
polypeptide chains, but you eat it.
I mean,
it tastes good. Heh-heh.
Why do you do that?
Do what?
Say something super smart
and then bail from it.
Can you keep a secret?
No.
But this time, sure, yeah.
Okay. Well, it was a really long
time ago, but I, too, was...
(WHISPERS)
a nerd.
Too?
When I was a little girl,
I wore a ponytail,
I had glasses,
and I was totally obsessed
with the science of weather.
SAM: Other girls
wanted a Barbie.
I wanted a Doppler Weather
Radar 2000 Turbo.
But all the kids used to taunt
me with this lame song.
It wasn't even clever.
KIDS SINGING: Four-eyes, four-eyes.
You need glasses to see
(SNICKERING)
Go on.
So I got a new look,
gave up the science-y
smart stuff,
and I was never
made fun of again.
And I still need these glasses,
but I never wear them.
I'll bet you look great
with glasses on.
Oh, I'm really not...
Oh. And on they go.
Whoa. What?
Nothing. Wait.
It's a Jell-O scrunchie.
And now, the reveal.
(MUSIC)
Wow.
I mean, you were okay before,
but now
you're beautiful.
No, I'm not. I can't go
out in public like this.
Well, why not?
I mean, this is the
real you, right?
Smart. Bespectacled.
Who wouldn't wanna see that?
You know, I've never met anyone
like you, Flint Lockwood.
Me either.
But about you.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Oh.
Hm.
FLINT'S VOICE ON PHONE:
Flint, you have a call.
Is your phone ringing?
That's weird.
Someone must've changed my ring.
Oh, it's the mayor.
Do you mind if I take this?
No, no, no.
Go ahead, take it. That's fine.
I'm sorry. It's important.
I should be going too.
It's getting late.
I'm just gonna step outside.
Ah!
(THUMP)
(MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
FLINT: Dad, you came.
I have so much to tell you.
Do I look all right?
You look great.
Come on, let's go. Ah!
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
FLINT: Dad, I almost
kissed a girl.
- It's Baby Brent, you know?
- FLINT: It was the coolest thing... Hi.
"Uh-oh. " I should be on the list.
Hey, Brian.
What? You're letting that guy in?
That guy's a nerd.
(MUSIC)
FLINT: Hey, how's it going?
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Oh, thank you. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
A toast. To Flint and
his delicious steaks.
Oh-ho, thanks. Thank you.
Very nice place.
Oh, wow. Thank you.
Flint Lockwood. Earl.
(LAUGHS)
TIM: So, uh, no roof.
Yep. You just hold
out your plate.
And I even made it
rain your favorite:
Meat. Mm.
(CHUCKLES)
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Okay.
So you know how the grand reopening
of the town is tomorrow?
Well, the mayor has asked
me to cut the ribbon.
He said my invention
saved the town.
Aren't you proud of me?
Uh...
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
Well, 'em,
doesn't this steak look
a little big to you?
Yeah, it's a big steak. I mean, every
steak is not exactly the same size.
Did you even hear
what I just said?
(UTENSILS CLATTER)
Son, look... Look around.
I'm not sure this is good for...
For people.
Maybe you should think about
turning this thing off.
It's making everybody happy.
Everybody except you.
When are you gonna accept
that this is who I am
instead of trying to get me to
work in some boring tackle shop?
Well,
you seem like you know
what you're doing, then.
I guess I'll just get
out of your way.
(GROANS)
FLINT: Get with the times, man.
I mean, there's no
pleasing that guy.
He just wants to take anything
good I do and just smoosh it.
Ah!
These are big hot dogs.
Man.
I mean, this isn't that bad.
Is it, Steve?
Yellow.
Ah. You're right, Steve.
The Dangeometer
is in the yellow.
I don't know what to do.
MAYOR: I do:
Declare these hot
dogs to be delicious!
(SCREAMS)
Oh, no. Whoa!
How did you get in here?
Tomorrow's the big day, Flint.
The entire town's fate is
resting on your food weather.
I'm thinking pasta.
Some light apps. I know
you won't let us down.
Well, Mr. Mayor, I think there's
something you should see.
What?
This is the molecular structure
of a hot dog that fell last week.
And this is the molecular structure
of a hot dog that fell today.
The machine uses
microwave radiation
to mutate the genetic
recipe of the food.
The more we ask it to make,
the more clouds it takes in,
the more radiation it emits, the more
these molecules could over-mutate.
I think that's why the
food is getting bigger.
Here's what I heard: "Blah, blah, blah."
Science, science,
science, bigger."
And bigger is better.
Everyone's gonna love
these new portion sizes.
Oh! I know I do.
My dad thinks I
should turn it off.
Geniuses like us are never
understood by their fathers, Flint.
But what if things go...
Who needs the approval
of one family member
when you can have it from
millions of acquaintances?
Not to mention that little
cutlet, Sam Sparks.
And me.
I've always felt that you
were like a son to me, Flint.
And I'm gonna be so proud of you
tomorrow when you cut that ribbon,
save the town,
and prove to everybody what
a great inventor you are.
So here's the cheese:
You can keep it going,
get everything
you've ever wanted,
and be the great man
I know you can be.
Or you can turn it off,
ruin everything,
and no one will ever like you.
It's your choice.
(WHISPERING)
Choice.
(SIGHS)
Okay.
(TYPING)
(WHIMPERS)
I mean, bigger is better,
right?
Oh, yeah.
MACHINE OVERLAPPING VOICES: Spaghetti.
Asparagus. Celery.
Garlic bread. Meatball. Shrimp.
(TALKING GIBBERISH)
(MUSIC)
- MAN 1: Looks safe to me.
- MAN 2: And sanitary too.
(MUSIC)
Whoa.
(BLOWS)
(DOPPLER 2000 BEEPING)
(ALL CHEERING)
MAYOR: Who's hungry?
Welcome, tourists,
to Chew And Swallow.
That is one big mayor.
Delight in our
nacho-cheese hot Springs.
Allow your kids to eat all
the junk food they want,
in our completely
unsupervised Kid Zone!
CAL: I've got
jellybeans for teeth.
And when the fun is done,
gaze upon the sunset cresting
over Mount Leftovers.
From which we're protected by a
presumably indestructible dam.
We've got people here today
from all around the world,
from as far as China
to West Virginia.
Also I think there's
some Canadians here.
Flint. You need to look at this.
Why aren't you on TV?
You're supposed to be broadcasting this.
There's a problem.
The food's getting bigger.
I know, it's great. Bigger portion sizes.
Everyone loves it.
I'm not sure we're doing
the right thing here.
What if we've bitten off
more than we can chew?
For the first time in my life, everybody
loves something that I've done.
Why can't you just
be happy for me,
and go say the weather or something.
Jeez.
MAYOR: And without further ado,
our town's hero and
my metaphorical son,
Flint Lockwood.
MAN 1: Yeah, Flint.
Thank you. Thank you, everyone.
- MAN 2: Sign my shrimp.
- FLINT: Thank you.
- MAN 3: Yeah. Yeah. Whoo!
- MAN 4: I love you.
I admire your quirkiness, dude.
Brent, we're gonna need you to
hand over the ceremonial scissors.
But...
No.
You can't. You can't take them.
Here you go.
No. I'm Baby Brent.
Uh-oh.
Put your clothes back on.
(CROWD BOOING)
Who am I?
Go ahead, Flint.
Everybody loves you.
CROWD CHANTING: Lockwood!
Lockwood! Lockwood!
Lockwood! Lockwood! Lockwood!
(ALL CHEERING)
CROWD: Lockwood! Lockwood!
Lockwood!
(GROANS)
(MUSIC)
CROWD: Lockwood! Lockwood!
Lockwood!
(CROWD CHEER)
(BIRDS SQUAWKING)
STEVE: Danger. Danger. Danger.
Salt-and-pepper wind?
Ugh!
Oregano.
Mamma Mia.
Sam, wait. No, I
can turn it off.
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
I can turn it off.
(SCREAMING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
FLINT: All right, kid,
it's all gonna be okay.
(SCREAMING)
Oh, no.
Pardon me. Pardon me.
FLINT: Excuse me.
Oh. No problem.
Whoa! Ha!
No.
(SCREAMS)
Gummi Bears. Not now, Steve.
(ALL SCREAMING)
MAN: Condiments?
Salt? Pepper?
Flint.
This is Sam Sparks, live
from Chew And Swallow,
where a spaghetti twister...
Ho. Ho.
Sam, hey, we love a good storm over
here, but you look like a nerd.
Patrick, several children are stranded
in the path of this tomato tornado.
My tummy hurts.
Cal!
Yikes. What is that, a scrunchie?
I haven't seen one of those since 1995.
What? We have an actual
weather emergency.
Ha-ha. Well, we'll get
right back to that storm,
and hopefully Sam'll look a
little more appealing. Boop.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYS OVER TV)
(BARKING)
(MUSIC)
Steve, we just have to upload the kill
code and then we'll shut down the...
Oh! What are you doing here?
I've been ordering dinner
for the last 10 minutes.
Why? Is something going on?
I've gotta stop the machine.
Everyone's in danger
because of me.
Oh, it can't be that bad.
No. Oh, ha... Well,
I'm out of here.
I can still stop the order
with the kill code.
(MONITORS BEEPING)
Sending kill code. I'm back.
FLINT: Got to get the button.
Ah!
Play. Fun. Fun. Play.
MAYOR: Hey, Flint.
It's been nice to beet you. Ha.
FLINT: That's a radish.
(BEEPS)
That was the only way to
communicate with the machine.
What exactly did you order?
A Vegas-style
all-you-can-eat buffet.
MACHINE: Jellybean. Watermelon.
Marshmallow. Pretzel. Sushi.
Cheeseburger. Pretzel. Egg salad.
Strawberry. Marshmallow.
Strawberry.
(COUGHS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
- JOE: Is everyone okay?
- PEOPLE: Yeah.
EARL: Help, somebody.
Help me, please.
It's my son.
We need a doctor.
Is anyone here a doctor?
Anyone?
MANNY: I am a doctor.
You are?
I was, back in Guatemala.
I came here for a better life.
Pretty great decision, eh?
How is he, doc?
He's in a food coma.
(CROWD GASPS)
Too much junk food.
I need a celery, stat.
Here you go.
(COUGHING)
Daddy?
Oh, Cal. Cal.
I love you, son.
(CAL VOMITING)
Looks like everything
turned out okay.
SAM: Not yet, it hasn't.
That twister was an amuse-bouche
compared to what's on the way.
WOMAN: What's an amuse-bouche?
Manny, patch us through.
Go.
Cute report, Nancy. Hey.
Hey. Four-eyes.
Can it, Patrick.
We are about to be in the epicenter
of a perfect food storm.
It's going to spread
across the globe.
I've calculated the Coriolis
acceleration of the storm system.
First, it'll hit New York,
then Paris,
then the Jiayuguan
Pass in eastern China.
And in four hours the entire northern
hemisphere will be one big potluck.
(MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
Flint?
(FLINT GROANING)
(SQUAWKING)
Flint?
Hey, Dad.
What are you doing?
Well, I tried to help everybody,
but instead I ruined everything.
(SNIFFLES)
I'm just a piece of junk.
So I threw myself away.
Along with all these
dumb inventions.
This is junk.
Oh, son. Listen, when your
boat is, when it's listing,
and if it's not running, you know...
Uh...
Don't worry, Dad, I get it.
Mom was wrong about me.
I'm not an inventor.
I should've just
quit when you said.
Well,
when it rains, you
put on a coat.
Dad, you know I don't
understand fishing metapho...
What?
My coat.
Come on, Steve.
We've got diem to carpe.
Kill code downloading.
Redesigning. Virtualizing.
Cutting.
Welding. Forging.
Wiring. Helping.
Testing.
Yes!
Flying Car 2.
Now with wings.
(HONKING MELODY)
BOTH: Whoa!
Hey, I had a weird
dream like this once.
MAN: I have a macaroni on my head.
Ah!
GIRL: Run.
ALL: No school!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALARM RINGING)
ANNOUNCER ON TV: Still nothing, nothing
in the bottom of the third inning.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Everyone.
I want to apologize.
Especially to you, Sam.
But I have a plan.
This flash drive
contains a kill code.
I will fly up into that food
storm, plug it into the machine,
and shut it down forever,
while you guys evacuate
the island, using brea...
MAYOR: This is all his fault.
Get him.
MAN 1: There he is! Get him!
MAN 2: Get Flint.
JOE: Let's rock his
car back and forth.
EARL: Hey!
This mess we're in
is all our faults.
Me, I didn't even
protect my own son.
Look, I'm as mad at
Flint as you are.
In fact, when he gets out of that
car, I'm gonna slap him in the face.
I know Flint Lockwood made the
food, but it was made-to-order.
And now it's time for all
of us to pay the bill.
(ALL CHEER)
Thank you, Earl. Ow!
Sorry. It's okay.
- Let's go build some boats.
- CROWD: Yeah.
MAN: I'm gonna go build a boat.
SAM: I'm coming with you.
You're gonna need someone to
navigate you through that storm.
I can't let you do this alone.
Oh, Sam, I'm so sorry.
Are you kidding?
Well, I just thought that we...
No.
Okay.
MANNY: You'll need a co-pilot.
You're a pilot too?
Yes. I am also a
particle physicist.
Really?
No, that was a joke.
I am also a comedian.
(FLINT, SAM & STEVE LAUGH)
- Let's do this thing.
- BRENT: I'm coming too.
Brent, that's okay.
No, it's not okay.
I've been coasting on my
fame since I was a baby.
But it was all just an illusion.
Maybe up there I'll find
out who I really am.
Uh... The car's
pretty full, so...
Yeah!
Brent.
Okay.
(SQUAWKING)
Good luck, son.
(WHIMPERING)
STEVE IN WAVERING VOICE: Steve.
SAM: Pea-soup fog.
FLINT: Manny, hit the wipers.
FLINT & SAM: Oh!
(DOPPLER 2000 BEEPING)
There's massive gastro-precipitation
accumulated around the machine.
It's almost as if it's...
Inside a giant meatball.
Water goes in the top,
a food hurricane comes
out the bottom.
BRENT: Glad I'm
wearing a diaper.
(MUSIC)
Anybody order pizza?
Oh!
FLINT: Hold on.
The pizza's chasing us?
Sentient food?
That's impossible.
Unless its molecular structure's
mutated into super food!
BOTH: That's been genetically
engineered to protect the FLDSMDFR.
- STEVE: Pizza.
- ALL: Ah!
STEVE: Pizza. Pizza. Pizza.
(GRUNTING)
That was close. I mean, can you
imagine if we lost this kill code?
Uh-oh.
(PHONE RINGS)
- Tim's Tackle Shop.
- FLINT: Dad.
You're okay, great. Um...
I need a favor. The fate of
the world depends on it!
Okay, then, skipper.
What do you need?
Go into my lab, get on my computer
and e-mail a file to my cell phone.
Um...
Uh...
All right.
(SCREAMING)
- MANNY: Want me to drive?
- FLINT: Yeah, okay.
(BRENT SCREAMING)
Wow. You're a lot better than me.
Uh-huh.
FLINT: Okay, here's the plan:
Sam and I will enter the meateroid
through the intake here,
which should lead us
straight to the FLDSMDFR.
Manny, you and Steve stay on the plane.
Don't spray that.
Once my dad e-mails me the kill
code, we'll destroy the machine
and rendezvous here at the
Western blowhole in...
How long until the world's destroyed?
About twenty minutes.
Just before then.
What about me, Brent?
What do I do?
Uh... You can be president
of the back seat.
Oh. Deploy hatch.
Car upside down, go.
Ladies first?
No?
All right. Ah!
Wait for me. Oh!
Great. Okay, I'm good.
SAM: As long as we stay on course, it
should be a straight shot to the...
(SAM GRUNTS THEN SCREAMS)
Yeah!
(ALL GRUNTING)
BRENT: We're a team.
Whoa.
We've landed here in some
kind of exhaust vent.
If we go this way, the Flamidabager
should be right down this air shaft.
Brent, get out of that pie.
What's that?
(INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
(SCREAMING)
Oh, boy.
Huh.
Huh. Oh.
COMPUTER: Welcome, Flint.
FLINT: That's fry oil.
(SCREAMING)
FLINT'S VOICE ON PHONE:
Flint, you have a call.
Flint, you have a...
Ah! Dad. Oh, okay, great.
On the screen there's a
file marked "kill code."
TIM: Wha...?
Move that into
my e-mail window,
type in my name, and press send.
Oh!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Window? Okay, Dad,
you see the thing that looks
like a little piece of paper?
Use the mouse to drag it.
Drag it? Drag it. Drag it.
Drag it.
Right? Okay. Great. Okay, great.
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
It's not dragging.
Drag it across the desktop.
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
That didn't do anything.
Of course it didn't!
You know what?
Ah!
EARL: Go, go, go.
Hoist those sails.
Toast that bread.
We are running out of time.
Let's move out. Go, go, go.
We can do it. Come on,
move it, move it.
Good job. That's what I'm talking about.
Everybody head to the docks.
(GRUNTS)
MAYOR: Wait, wait.
I have an important
announcement.
See you, suckers.
Whoo-hoo. Bon voyage.
And bon appétit.
(MAKES MUNCHING SOUNDS)
(CAL GRUNTING)
- EARL: Cal.
- REGINA: Calvin.
EARL: Cal, get back here.
- CAL: Foodalanche.
- EARL: Cal.
I'm not gonna lose you again.
Baby.
(CAL SCREAMING)
Hold on tight, Calvin.
(GRUNTS)
Mm.
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
Everybody head South. We gotta
stay ahead of that storm.
(RUMBLING)
Now what?
Just click "send."
Flint, the Fliminadifiserser's
right down there!
- Dad, hurry.
- TIM: Send. Send.
Oh, wait.
Dad? Dad?
Can you hear me?
Dad?
Hey, guys?
(CLUCKING)
Holy crap balls.
Go, go, go.
(FLINT SCREAMING)
Aw. I don't know. I think
they're kind of cute.
I mean, this one just walked
right up to me and...
He's got me!
(IN UNISON)
They ate Brent.
Dad, I'm surrounded by
man-eating chickens right now.
FLINT: So if this is goodbye,
thanks for trying
to set me straight.
Figured it out a
little late, I guess.
Okay, bye.
(DIAL TONE BUZZING)
(GRUNTING)
(BEEPS)
Dad.
Hey, give me that phone back.
(CLUCKING)
BRENT: Uh-oh!
Ah! Ha-ha-ha!
FLINT: Baby Brent?
I'm not Baby Brent anymore.
I'm Chicken Brent.
And I'm finally
contributing to society.
Crotch kick.
(YELLS)
Now go, you crazy kids,
and save the world.
You did it, Chicken Brent.
You really did it.
Go, go, go.
(BRENT GRUNTING)
It should be right
down this hole.
That's peanut brittle.
If either one of us touches it,
we'll go into anaphylactic shock.
Actually, I'm not entirely
allergic to peanuts.
I might have just said that
to get you to like me.
So you really thought
having allergies
would make you more attractive?
Eh...
Mustache.
Mus... Mmp!
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
- Sesame bagel.
- MAN 1: Hey, taxi.
- MAN 2: Taxi.
- MAN 3: Taxi.
I asked for extra mustard. Ah!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
I was right.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(IN BRITISH ACCENT)
Hot tea?
MAN: Did he say hot tea?
WOMAN: "You are about to be
crushed by a giant corn."
Run!
(ALL SCREAMING)
It looks like the food storm is
following an unusual pattern
of hitting the world's
famous landmarks first,
and is now spreading to
the rest of the globe.
What the what?
Hurry up, guys.
FLINT: After I plug my phone into
the FLDSMDFR and destroy it,
I'll tug on the licorice twice and
you'll pull me back up, okay?
Sounds great.
Ah!
(SCREAMING)
SAM: Oh, no.
(GRUNTS)
You... You got cut, didn't you?
Uh... It's just a scratch.
Brent, you need to take Sam back to
the plane to get her an allergy shot.
Just a second.
What? No.
Let go, Sam. I'm not
gonna let you go.
Flint, you'll be
stuck down there.
It's not ideal, no.
Come with us. We'll start over.
We'll live underground.
Use bacon for clothes.
Sam, that's not a
very good plan.
It is if it means I
don't have to lose you.
Look, I like you, okay?
Like... Like, as a friend?
No.
Like, "like you" like you.
Me too.
But about you.
Goodbye, Sam.
Flint. No!
BRENT: Hang on, Sam.
Dr. Manny's got the
medicine for your face.
(SCREAMS)
MACHINE: Pickles.
(COUGHS)
Beets.
Banana.
Strawberry.
(SCREAMS)
- SAM: Manny, we're on our way. Hurry.
- MANNY: Hang on, Sam.
I'm circling the blowhole.
(SPEAKS IN SPANISH)
Scared.
(MUSIC)
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
Gummi Bears.
GUMMI BEAR: Play with us, play with us.
Eat us, eat us.
STEVE: Hungry!
Hungry. Gummi Bears. Gummi Bears.
Gummi Bears. Steve hungry. Hungry.
Steve starving. Hungry.
Hungry. Starving.
Whoa!
(BRENT SCREAMING)
BRENT: Manny. Where are you?
(SCREAMS)
(WHIMPERS)
(CHICKENS CLUCKING)
(SCREAMS)
(GIBBERING)
She touched a peanut or something.
Oh, boy.
(HUMMING)
(ALARM BUZZES)
MACHINE: Corn. Yikes!
(MACHINE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
FLINT WHISPERING: Grabbing.
Tying. Throwing.
Waiting.
Swinging.
(GRUNTING)
(ALARM BUZZING)
Sorry, old friend.
The kitchen's closed.
Yah!
CAT ON MONITOR: Fight the power!
Dad.
No.
Ah! Whoa! Whoa!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(MUSIC)
When it rains, you put on a coat
of Spray-On Shoes.
Yeah.
SAM: Just...
There were chickens...
(GASPS)
Where's Flint?
No!
I know, kid.
I know.
(ALL CHEERING)
- CAL: Cool.
- EARL: Yeah. All right.
(CHEERS & APPLAUSE)
(MUSIC)
(SIGHS)
Flint?
I'm sorry.
Oh.
(WHIMPERS)
Your son was a great man.
(RATBIRDS SQUAWKING)
(SQUAWKING)
Steve. Steve.
Flint. Brent.
Flint. Cal.
Steve. Flint.
- Earl.
- MAN: Flint.
- You guy.
- STEVE: Steve.
(CHEERS & APPLAUSE)
Sam.
Flint.
Flint. Flint.
Dad. Steve.
Flint.
Oh.
Look, when you...
When you cast your line,
if it's not straight... Um...
SAM: Oh, for crying out loud.
(SQUEALS)
TIM'S VOICE OVER SPEAKER:
I'm proud of you, Flint.
I'm amazed that someone
as ordinary as me
could be the father of someone
as extraordinary as you.
You're talented, you're
a total original.
And your lab is breathtaking.
Your mom, she always knew you
were going to be special.
And if she were alive
today, she'd tell us both:
"I told you so. " Ha-ha.
Now, uh, look, when I
take this thing off,
and you hear me make
a fishing metaphor,
just know that fishing
metaphor means:
I love my son.
I love you too, Dad.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(SOBBING)
So where were we?
You were about to kiss me.
Were you gonna kiss me back?
Why don't you find out?
Because I don't want to go for
it and then get shut down again.
Just kiss me. You know...
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(ALL APPLAUDING)
BRENT: Yeah! I'm a chicken!
(RATBIRDS SQUAWKING)
This was not well thought out.
(MIRANDA COSGROVE'S
"RAINING SUNSHINE" PLAYING)
(MUSIC)
http://subscene.com/u/659433
Improved by: @Ivandrofly