My name is Flint Lockwood
My whole life..
I always wanted to be
a great inventor.
Just like my hero.
The Scientifically Wonderful
World of Science.
With your host, Chester V.
Welcome back, science friends.
You know, I have devoted my life
to inventing the future.
But every dream has a beginning.
I still remember my first invention:
The humble Food Bar.
It was like Chester V
was speaking directly to me
using the language of science
Now look at us.
Our new Food Bar XL
with flavor crystals.
Still making people happy
after all these years
Now, kids, you'll almost certainly
never be me.
But, remember, there's no such thing
as small science
Only small scientists!
We love you, Chester V!
Speaking of small scientists,
say goodbye, Barb
Goodbye, Barb
Can your ideas change the world?
Yes.
Just like Chester V
my dream was to make the
world a better place
Spray On Shoes!
How you gonna
get them off, nerd?
Unfortunately, a lot of
people didn't believe in me
But I never gave up
And eventually
I invented this:
A machine that could
turn water into food
Cheeseburger
It's called the Flint Lockwood
Diatonic Super Mutating
Dynamic Food Replicator
Or, for short
The FLDSMDFR
Because of my invention's
food weather
I finally made the
world a better place
Yeah!
I love it!
Or so I thought
When the weather evolved into
a disaster of epic portions
and the machine started
creating dangerous living food
I had to face the truth:
It was time to put an
end to my FLDSMDFR
Che Che Che Che
Cheese
By destroying
my greatest invention
I made something even better:
Friends!
You made me very proud, son
Thank you, Dad Sorry
Sam Sparks, in the eight minutes
since we saved the world
I've had time to reflect
And I think you and I
should have a place together
A Place?
A place where we work
You think we work together?
I do
Awesome! Yes!
We could build a lab
With cool weather
forecasting devices!
We can invent fantastic machines
like the FLDSMDFR
Yeah!
But not that one No
Not ever Never, ever, ever!
What shall we call our lab?
How about Sparks-wood?
Sparks-wood
Sparks-wood is gonna need
some security
And I can be your mascot!
And I can be your dad
There are many ways
in which I can help
Can't forget you, lab partner
Steve!
Where'd he get the brown crayon?
This could be our
future Oh, yeah!
Greetings, friends
And namaste
Is that? Chester V?
Mustache
Please have some humanitarian aid
as a gesture of our goodwill
Chester V!
Your lab vest looks even cooler
in person!
Thank you The lack of sleeves
frees up my arms to do this
Hand, what did you do?
There's nothing wrong with your hand,
young Lockwood
You see, I am merely a hologram
of the real Chester V
The United Nations has asked
me and my Thinkquanauts
to assist in the cleanup
and containment
of the leftovers all over the world
Including your Swallow Falls
We'll get started on
the cleanup right away
As soon as you all leave
What? You need us to leave?
Listen up, ghost man
you expect us to skedaddle from our
homes because of some nasty leftovers?
Yes Yes, I do
Son, you can't argue
with yellow police tape
Everybody back up!
Listen to ghost man
But do not fret
All of you will be
temporarily relocated
to sunny San Franjose
California!
The home of Live Corp!
On my word as a hologram
you shall all return home
before you know it
Except for you, Flint Lockwood
Me? Why?
You are going
Wait, wait, wait No, no, no
Where am I going?
Oh, please tell me!
Just give it a second He's buffering
You are going to join me
at Live Corp
and help us make the world
a better place
Sir, that's all I've ever wanted
But I can't
On account of making a promise
two minutes ago
to build a lab with my friends, sir
I understand, Lockwood
But if you become
a Thinkquanaut like me
then all your dreams will come true
You have to do this!
What about our dream?
Flint, this is a once in a life-time
opportunity
We're all behind you
Are you guys sure?
Sure
This is the best day ever!
Sir, I've taken care of everything
The locals have been evacuated
Splendid And the inventor?
Oh, he took the job
Outstanding!
Now we can keep an eye on him
He has no idea of our real plan
Contact me as soon as Operation
Capture the Invention succeeds
Live Corp
Cheeseburger
Oh, big day, big day!
Big day, big day
big day! Yes!
Wake up, Steve!
Steve
Do I look like a future Thinkquanaut?
Morning there, skipper
You want a sardine scramble?
No, thanks! Can't be late!
Flint! Ask that Chester V when
he thinks we can go home again
Morning, Sam!
Morning, Flint! Are you ready
for your first day?
Yeah! Are you?
Sam?
Well, this is me Good luck
with your new jobs, guys
Good luck, Flint!
Break a leg, Flint!
Bye!
Good morning, Flint Lockwood
and lab partner
I'm Barb
I know, I'm a huge fan
Monkey
Excuse me
I'm an ape One of Chester V's
most brilliant innovations
An orangutan with a human brain
within my ape brain
Like a turducken
I'll be your welcome ambassador
Soy latte?
Okay
Coffee and milk?
Are you ready to
live? Oh, am I!
Monkey
Ape Follow me, boys
Welcome to Live Corp
There are caffeine stations
every 10 feet
Soy-free soy latte?
Thanks!
Hot
Not too bad yourself, monkey
Caffeine patches
are available 24 hours
And our mocha-yoga classes
are offered in beginner or grande
Over here, indoor sports
Those are encouraged
Oh, cool! I've never played volleyball
Well, neither have they
You'll fit right in!
Can your ideas change the world?
Behold, the motivation pod
Can your ideas?
I know, right?
Quinoa latte?
Absolutely!
Can your ideas
change the world?
Yes, Chester V poster, they can!
Mine too!
So can mine!
I have great ideas
Absolutely! I've got my idea pants on
Thinkquanauts! Awesome!
Hey! Excuse me
I'm so looking forward
to working with you guy
That's where we belong, Steve
Anxious!
That's not even a possibility
until our next vesting ceremony
What's that?
That's where Chester V
handpicks a great inventor
and makes him into a Thinkquanaut
When? When?
Next one's in six months,
so submit your ideas
and who knows?
He might choose you
Really?
Hot chocolate with
double whipped whipped cream?
Thanks Happy inventing!
We're gonna have to get used to
that landing
Okay, Steve, we have six months
until the vesting ceremony
Let's do this thing
Can
That's the spirit, Steve!
Say goodbye
to ice cubes
with the Re Freeze a Fan!
Can your ideas change the world?
The Forkenknifenspooninator!
Can your ideas
change the world?
The Grocery Deliverator!
Can your ideas change the world?
Invisible coffee table!
Flint
Can your ideas
change the world?
Flint!
The Celebrationator!
A party in a box for any occasion
Okay, Steve, time to celebrate!
Celebrate!
Flint!
Happy birthday, Tim Lockwood!
Here you go, Dad Hope you like it
Steve picked it out
Steve!
Yeah Yeah!
Okay, like we practiced
When I'm up on stage getting my vest
you hit the red button
when I say "celebrate"
Celebrate!
Careful, Steve!
This is a loaded party in ab ox
Hello, Team Live Corp!
It's a pleasure to welcome you
to our annual Thinkquanaut
vesting ceremony!
Chester V!
I have built the coolest, hippest
company in the world
As you all know, the Food Bar
is the lifeblood of this company
And this year, I've challenged myself
to reinvent taste
So in two short weeks
we shall release the new
Live Corp Food Bar!
Version 8.0!
Yes!
And now, without
further ado, who will be this year's
newest Live Corp Thinkquanaut?
Yeah!
We have received thousands
of invention submissions
and today, one of them
will be deemed
Thinkquanaut worthy
Thank you, Barb
This person comes from an island
He's got a memorable mop
of unruly hair
Hair Hair!
That's me!
Our newest Live Corp
Thinkquanaut is:
Flint
Yeah!
Ly McCallahan!
No
Crikey blikey! Yes!
For inventing a zero emission
car that runs on cute
This is the greatest day of my life!
Didgeridoo! I'm finally a real inventor!
Sorry, Steve No reason to celebrate
Celebrate!
Wait, Steve, no, no, no No!
Hi, Sam, it's Flint
I see you're live on TV
with a tornado
Probably why you're not
answering the phone
Thinkquanaut? I think not
Please call me back
Okay Bye!
Bad news! Sir, we lost contact
with Search Teams X and Y
What?
Yeah!
The situation is
grim, sir Still no sign
of the FLDSMDFR
Should I send in Team Z?
Are you mad, Barb?
We'll be all out of alphabet
Look, we're running low
on Thinkquanauts We need
someone expendable
Someone who knows the island
inside and out
Someone who's smart, but still naive
Someone who idolizes me has
recently hit rock bottom
and will now do
just about anything I ask
Where are we gonna find
someone so desperate?
I think we already have
Sprinkles!
Fire!
Flint, who's number one?
Ta da!
Hey, Flint, I got your message
Oh, no, what happened to you?
Flint, everyone gets humiliated
on national television
It's not that big a deal
Yeah, but not everyone
gets humiliated
in front of their childhood hero
I'll never be a real
inventor in Chester's eyes
Mom gave me this lab coat because
she always dreamed
I'd do great things
Now I guess I won't Now
that's a big bucket of churn
Flint, you don't need
Chester's approval
You can still make the world a
better place without an orange vest
I don't get vests
Is it winter on your torso
and summer on your arms?
For what it's worth, the people
who really care about you
think you look great in your lab coat
Good night, Mr Lockwood
Good night, my dear
Hey, look, son
This Chester V guy
He promised us we'd be home
before we know it Well
we darn sure know it
and we're not home
So I say you, me and your friends
we take the boat
We can go fishing every day
And if there's still a mess on the island,
we can go clean it up ourselves
Dad, please I'm not into fishing
And cleanup? You're way too old
to be doing that kind of work
I'm only 49
Flint Lockwood, please
Oh, Flint
There's Could you
come to the door, please?
I think it's that monkey
in your poster
What? No!
Barb?
Good day
I'm afraid I have something very
important to discuss with you
Live Corp
Chester V wants to see me?
Follow me
Young Lockwood
Chester V Sir
I can explain everything
I thought I was gonna meet
the real Chester V
You are..
Oh, not me Him
Yes, it's me
Sorry about that
My holograms and I were having
an urgent brainstorming session
Mr V! You're real!
I'm so excited to get this opportunity
to show you my inventions
Hold on Hold on That's not
why I brought you here tonight
Our cleanup operation
back on Swallow Falls
has met with
unexpected complications
This is a photograph
before we began our cleanup
And this was three days ago
It gets worse, Flint
There's only two of us left
We need help
What is that thing?
Cheesy
It appears to be
a living cheeseburger
with french fry legs
and sesame seed eyes
Living food?
Oh, no This could only mean
one thing
The FLDSMDFR
survived the explosion
and it's still operating
This is what worries me most
They're trying to learn to swim
If they succeed and
get to the mainland
they will destroy monuments
all around the world
including the one monument
your food storm didn't destroy
Not Lady Liberty! I've gotta destroy
the FLDSMDFR But how?
Well, my Thinkquanauts
have invented
this
The BS-USB
Or BS-USB
A Bifurcating Systematic
Universal Stop Button!
Precisely It would destroy the
machine and everything it created
But we cannot find your FLDSMDFR
We've searched
everywhere and failed
Chester, I'll find the machine
I invented it I can fix this!
Brilliant!
But are you sure you want to
take this on alone?
Yes! Wait, did you say "alone"?
Alone it is, then
If you succeed, you'll be more
than just a Thinkquanaut
You'll be my hero
Your hero?
Yes, my hero
Your mission must be kept a secret
We don't wanna create
a worldwide panic
You mustn't tell anyone, not even
your closest friends and family
Sir, I won't tell a soul
Sam! Sam, Sam, Sam!
I gotta tell you a secret! Sam!
Big news I'm going to Swallow Falls
to destroy the FLDSMDFR
which is creating
deadly food monsters
which are trying to learn to swim
so they can attack Lady Liberty!
Sam?
Wait, you're doing this alone?
Yeah Please don't tell Dad If he finds
out I'm going back to Swallow Falls
he's gonna wanna come too
Well, I'm coming
What? No! I promised Chester V
I would go alone
There's no talking you out of this?
Nope Wait
Sam, it's gonna be deadly dangerous
with a good chance of death
And that's why we'll need help
Triple decaf mochaccino boba latte
with skim soy and nutmeg sprinkle?
I'd like to order something strong
Wait your turn, fancy pants
Flint Lockwood
and Sam Sparks!
And Steve too!
Juicy!
Earl, we need your help
Swallow Falls is overrun
with deadly food monsters
Hey
where's my coffee?
Coffee? I'm not a barista
I'm a polista!
Let's ride!
Can I come too, Dad?
Son, you are my beautiful,
precious little angel
But I cannot let you come with me
Not until you get
your first chest hair
I have chest hair
It's just like mine
Wait a minute
That's not a chest hair
That's cupcake frosting
Tell your mom
I'm getting our home back
What's up?
Sponge
Forceps
A swab
Manny We need your help.
I can drop everything
Camera
Chick 'n' sushi
Get it while it's cold
Yo, Chicken Brent!
In the flesh
Swallow Falls is in trouble
Will you help us?
You bet I will I just need someone
to cover my shift
Thanks, tree
Okay, gang
We'll be traveling to the island
using my Grocery Deliverator!
All right, who wants to go first?
Hungry
Yes, Steve, hungry for adventure
See you on the island,
my brave lab partner
Afraid!
It worked!
Banana! Banana! Banana! Steve!
I guess it only works on food
I gotta fix that
Ahoy there, skipper, my boy
Dad Mr Lockwood?
Dad, no How did you know
we were here?
I could see you from the apartment
Flint, if you're going home, so am I
The island's gonna be
very dangerous
I was born on the island, and I wanna
die on that island, just like your mom.
Besides, I know that place like
the inside of a tackle box I wanna help
No!
Flint, let him help.
The man does have a boat
Which is twice as many boats
as we have
Fine But we'll get there faster
if we use the Grocery Deliverator
Steve!
Okay, okay, we'll take the boat!
Shoving off!
Ninety nine buckets of chum on a boat
Ninety nine buckets
Of chum
Nineteen buckets of chum on a boat
Nineteen buckets of chum
You hold your nose
And out one goes
There's 18 buckets of chum on a boat
We'll be there in two flaps
of a sardine's fluke!
Thanks, Dad!
Okay, when we land at Swallow Falls
our first objective is to get to my lab
I can use my old computer to pinpoint
the FLDSMDFR's location
Once we find it, we can shut it down
with the utterly irreplaceable BS-USB
What if you don't find it?
I have to It's my machine
If the world gets destroyed
by these, it's my fault
I can't let that happen
Land ho!
If we work together,
this should be easy as
Pie
Oh, no! We're Toast!
French toast!
This is totally
Bananas!
I was gonna say "nuts,"
but now I'm afraid to
Home!
No! Steve, wait!
The jungle's no place for a monkey
Home, home, home!
Manny, are you getting this?
I certainly am Flint
Look! The climate
has shifted dramatically
to allow this much vegetation
to grow!
Sam! Rat-birds!
Okay, then All ashore
that's going ashore
Dad, this place is really dangerous
I'd feel better if you stayed here
on the boat where it's safe
Safe? I wanna help
I'd never forgive myself if you
got eaten by a cheespider
He's right, Tim Lockwood
Don't worry, we'll get your home back
Well, fine
Thanks, Dad We'll try to be back
before suppertime, okay?
Sure
Look what's happened to our town
Look
There's my angel son
Cal's old preschool
My old van
Look! An old thing
that I've never seen before!
That's where
the Thinkquanauts were
attacked by a cheespider
It's like a cheesy spider web,
made of
cheese Let's get out of here!
No, wait What if there's
a survivor in there?
Stand back, everybody
I'm gonna cut the cheese
That was the cheese
Hello? Anybody in here?
Sorry
That is the biggest strawberry
I've ever seen in my life
Is it heavy?
Yeah But other than that
it looks like a perfectly normal,
fresh, delicious strawberry
Nwoo?
It's moving!
Oh, that was a close one
You got a little someone
stuck to your pants
Get it off! Get it off me! Sam! Sam!
Hey, wait, wait Stop!
Sam, don't touch it! Put it down!
Put it down!
Look at him
Seriously?
I think I'll name him Barry!
Okay, Sam, could you please
put "Barry" down?
Look, we have to get to the FLDSMDFR
so we can shut it down
with this utterly irreplaceable
BS-USB
Hey! That's not for you!
I need that Please?
That BS-USB is really important
Nwoo?
Nwoo Yes Nwoo?
Hi, Nwoo Hey, you wanna
hand it to me, buddy?
I beg you
Please?
Nwoo
Nwoo, Nwoo Yes Yes There you go
No!
Don't let him get away!
Stop!
Gotcha
Nwoo?
Here, you take it, you take it
You're gonna have to carry him
until he passes the BS-USB
And by pass, you mean
Yes Look, we better get a move on
before we run into any more
of these creatures
It's so beautiful
It's enough to make a grown man cry
But not this man
Get back in there, tear
Wow, I can't believe
the FLDSMDFR created
all of this
Where's Barry?
Just a little bit closer
I can get him
Come on, Earl, faster
Look at the mangoes
You mean flamingos
Flamangos!
There's a bunch of shrimp!
They look like chimpanzees
Shrimpanzees!
Those are some
tasty looking jellyfish!
What's that one over there?
That's just a tomato
Barry!
Come on!
Chester gave me that BS-USB
It's really important
Shrimpanzee Steve
Shrimpanzee Shove
Steve
There's a leek in the boat!
Hold on, everyone
This ain't gonna be no picnic
Stop! Get back here!
Keep it steady, Earl
Watermelophants!
Barry, grab my hand!
Barry!
Freeze, berry man
Thanks, Earl
Okay, come here
You have caused enough trouble
for one day
Susheep!
Cantalopes
I can't believe your machine
reprogrammed itself to create
this entire ecosystem of living food
How is that even possible?
I have no idea
Best we don't think about it
The world should know about this
Manny, is your camera still working?
Of course I've been
rolling since we
landed So much for
keeping this a secret
We can't let these friends
tell the world anything
What we need to do is go there.
And separate Flint from his friends
so we can manage the situation
Champion!
Brilliant idea
Way to go, Chester Thank you
Barb, you take care of that weather girl
But, sir
I'm a scientist
That's why I need you
I want the same brilliant mind
that solved the unified field theory
to help me help Live Corp
Consider it done, sir
Good monkey
To the Helpicopter
Oh, Earl
Pull over there
Duck!
Duck? I love
Yeah!
You guys, that wasn't so bad
Yeah, well, be thankful
we didn't run into a
Cheespider!
Run!
Cheesy Cheesy Cheesy
Manny!
Wait for me!
I'm glad you still wearing
that diaper
I wish I brought a fresh one!
Hey, guys! Down this alley!
Oh, no! Dead end
Ghost man?
Greetings, and namaste
Chester V! You're here!
That's right.
Young Lockwood And by the
looks of things just in time.
One minute later, and we
would have been food for that food
Flint, I thought you said you were
going to complete this mission alone
Can I say something?
Apparently you can
This is Barb, my number two
Why are you carrying a strawberry
in your backpack, miss?
Stand back, everyone!
Hey, hey, hey, stop
You're scaring him
Scaring him?
Oh, please, it's probably
got a mouth full of fangs
Now you're scaring me
I've been carrying him
and he hasn't hurt anyone
I'm sorry Are you a scientist?
Matter of fact, I am
She's a meteorologist
Meteorology Oh, I love it
The science of smiling and having
pretty hair while you point at a map
It's a very important job
Meteorology is
a comprehensive analysis
Ladies, ladies Please
I'm sure we can all agree
that one of you is a scientist
Young Lockwood
why was your lady friend carrying this
rabid little strawberry in her backpack?
Why is the strawberry guy in
the backpack? Well, that's funny
It's You know what he did?
He.. He ate the BS-USB
Not the BS-USB
I'm on it
She's got a knife!
If you touch a leaf on his head
Step away from the berry, madam
That orange hairy lady
scared the jam out of him!
Nwoo?
Oh, no, it's jammed
Lick Lick Lick
Oh, thanks, Steve
Young Lockwood
The world could've been destroyed
because of the actions
of one sinister strawberry
We cannot allow any more mistakes
like this
It won't be long before
those malicious melons
pernicious pickles and belligerent
burgers learn to swim
and make their way
to the mainland
What is your plan?
I need to get back to my lab so I
can make contact with the FLDSMDFR
Brilliant!
I'll lead the way
No, we'll lead the way
Safe, safe, safe
I believe my Sentinels of Safety
are better equipped to lead us
in their robo suits
Nwoo?
"I'll be back before supper"
What a bunch of baloney
Just leave me on the boat
without any food
I know a place where
I can get something to eat
There she is
Home sweet home
What?
There's no sardines?
Had to be looters
Vintage Baby Brent
Oh, chum
No, no!
Yeah
I like them too I do I love them
Mine No, no Mine
Off Off Mine
No, no, mine Mine Off
Hey, hey, hey Easy, you guys
Come on, you could lose an eye
Look, I tell you what You want more
sardines? I can get you more sardines
Hey, thanks for loaning me
these skinny jeans, Flint
Those aren't skinny jeans Nope
My feet are turning purple
Is that bad?
Bananostrich!
Go, go, go! Come on, Brent!
Banana! Banana! Banana!
That bunch of bananostriches
nearly split us
Are you okay?
Oh, my gosh
My house!
Home, home, home!
Oh, my gosh
Your lab!
Oh, crap balls
We can't go up there, Flint Lockwood
That dangly, upsy downsy lab's
not to code
I've got to, if I'm gonna find
the FLDSMDFR
We can do it .Those load bearing vines
will be able to support a small team
Onwards and upwards!
Right, sir To the lab!
Sentinels, keep the locals safe
I'll keep them safe
Hey, guys! Where you going?
Guys! Hey
wait for me!
A little help?
Spooky
Spooky is right, Steve
I say this laboratory of yours
is a wonder of engineering
Really?
Thank you, sir
Initiating backup power
Welcome, Flint
Whoa, my computer's dead
The fate of the world is depending
on us Think, Lockwood
Well, if I could pull
the hard drive, there's enough
equipment in this
lab that I could build
a tracking device
Flint!
I say, young Lockwood,
what extraordinary
underpants
Thank you, sir They're
my Wedgie proof underwear
I invented them when I was 6
I had no idea we were so alike
Except I invented mine
when I was 3
You guys have been wearing the same
underwear since you were kids?
'Yes!
Excuse me
How do you expect us
to get the hard drive
with all that electrified water?
We dangle!
Come, Lockwood, give the monkey
your underpants
What?
Lay on
young Lockwood
Yes!
You know, hanging from
my underpants in this space
brings back so many memories
I too built my lab up high
to keep the bullies out!
You were
You were bullied too?
Absolutely
People like us
are always bullied
Sometimes I wish I'd kept
my bullies around
Really?
So I could crush them
with my success
Just like you did with that man baby
You mean Brent?
Sure, he used to be a bully,
but he's my friend now
Friend?
A bully can never be your friend
Never?
Remember
the ancient Chinese proverb:
"Stew offered by a bully
is poisoned broth"
Wow, stew
I have so much to learn
Mission accomplished!
Indeed, young Lockwood Indeed
Help!
Help! Come on, guys Get me out!
You okay, Earl?
My chest hairs
have been tingling all day
Don't worry Live Corp
Sentinels have danger
sensing fibers built
into their chest plates
Bravo, Lockwood
With luck, we'll survive the night
Sounds like midnight snacks
Dr Manny! This is delicious!
I call it Manny's Gorilla Stew
So how do you make a gorilla stew?
You keep it waiting for two hours
Hey, guys Oh, that smells good
Hey, Flint! Wanna try some of this
special stew? I saved you a bowl
It's killer
Killer stew
No!
Thank you
Brent
Ever since that ghost man
showed up
Flint Lockwood's been acting
Jerky
He rejected my stew
No one has ever rejected my stew
I'm gonna go talk to him
Flint, wait up Yeah, Sam?
Is something wrong?
Yeah, we blew a fuse
You blew a fuse
Why are you being so weird
to your friends?
What? I haven't been weird
You karate chopped
Manny's stew out of Brent's hands
You hurt their feelings
Sam, you wouldn't understand
I do understand,
but you're forgetting that:
"A bully turned friend
will be friend to the end"
Listen, Brent came here to help you
We all did
And you're acting like
we're just in your way
Remember, we work together
That weather girl is ruining our plan
I just need more time, sir
We don't have more time
If we don't get the FLDSMDFR
in the next 48 hours
we'll miss our deadline
to release Food Bar 8.0
I'll be a laughingstock!
Sir, let me handle this
Never send a monkey
to do Chester work
I'll take care of it
Okay, guys, we're here
Hey, hey, hey!
That is not for you
All right, let's get to it
Okay
You got this, right?
Okay Then you wanna put
one of these on there, like that
No, no, no
No, don't eat that That's bad
You'll hurt yourself
Hey, hey, easy! Stop picking
on your brother, will you?
How would you like it
if he was shoving you?
Okay, now watch
Are you watching?
One and two and three!
Catch the big one!
Yeah, good, huh?
It's called fishing
Out on my boat
With a pickle that likes dill
The frowny one's sour
He's a real bitter pill
She's so sweet
With her onion pet Pearl
Teaching pickles to fish
That's my crazy world
I tell you, if only Flint liked fishing
as much as you guys
Why am I talking to a pickle?
Dangerous food creatures detected
Stay put We'll find and destroy them
Barry!
You can't be here
You better hide him
Okay, gang! Today's the day
We find the FLDSMDFR
Sam, I was thinking about
what you said last night
Nwoo?
What?
Me too
Right Listen, I have been acting weird, but
it's only because I'm under a lot of pressure.
Nwoo?
What?
So true!
But I'm also doing this for us
You see
I still want Sparks-wood
to happen, but it can't
Not until I become a great inventor
like Chester V
Flint, you don't have to
prove anything
Lockwood! How goes the inventing?
Very good, sir I was up all night
making this
I call it the Flint Lockwood
Food Jungle
Topographical Pointing Machine
Or
The FLFJTPM! Brilliant!
Oh, thank you, sir Follow the beam,
find the machine
All I have to do now
is cut the leg holes
Well maybe it's better here
Great idea, Sam
And, guys, you can help me by
Excuse us Your friends are
distracting you from our mission
Distracting?
My chest hairs just
don't trust that Chester
We should be hunting
the FLDSMDFR, not chitchatting
But, sir, I ..You're heading into the
deepest, darkest part of the jungle
You need to focus on
saving the world.
Be a hero.
Okay You're right, sir
Excellent! Let's go!
Okay, Barry, time to go home now
Okay Okay
Okay, one more hug, Barry
Barry?
Right! Barry
You Barry
Barry
And I'm Sam Sparks
Saspa
Right! Sam
Come on, Sam!
Coming!
Okay, Barry, time to go home now
Now go
Now you go on home
Bye
Saspa
Hot dog Hot dog
Tacodile! Supreme!
Holy guacamole!
I got this, bro!
I'm okay!
Up there! Hurry, Sam!
Barb!
You Okay?
Freeze!
Come on, let's go!
Let's get out of here!
Bravo, young Lockwood, bravo!
A mother?
Sam!
SaSpa!
Butter
Park-ay
Almost there
The FLDSMDFR
should be just across
this syrup bog This is syrup?
Syrup is my favorite
Darn mosquitoasts!
Don't worry, man baby
They, like all the other abominable
food monsters will soon be no more
Wait, Flint!
What if we're making a big mistake?
Mistake?
About shutting off the FLDSMDFR
Some of these creatures,
they're incredible..
Incredibly dangerous. We were just
attacked by a giant tacodile
He's right, Sam I mean, we were
almost eaten by a cheespider
It doesn't mean we have to
destroy all of them
Some of the food's
actually been friendly
It is true The dessert creatures
are especially sweet
Okay Maybe we
Mosquitoast!
Was gonna bite you
See? Even the tiniest creatures
are attacking us
The only reason they're
biting is because of the drop
in barometric pressure
Bugs do that before a storm And by
the look of those nimbostratus clouds
Miss Sparks, we are
not talking about the weather
We are talking about food here
Dangerous food that does not
have human emotion
Food that is not friendly
Food that cannot love!
Flint
we should be studying
the food animals, not killing them
What if he's wrong?
The choice is yours, son
Live up to your full potential
or walk away and let the food
monsters destroy Lady Liberty
Sam, finding that FLDSMDFR
and saving the world
that's what matters
Really? Our opinion doesn't matter?
Of course it does!
Yes! Yes, it matters
But just not right now
Wrong answer Toast
Yeah? Well, I guess
this doesn't matter either
young Lockwood
I'll just
see you back on the boat
Wait! Sam!
Wait, please!
No! No Sam! Come back!
Come back, Sam, no!
No, Sam!
Sam! Sam!
Sand!
Hey, Earl, would you talk to her?
You bet I will
Hey, Sam! Wait for me!
Goodbye, Senor Lockwood
Bye, Flint
Steve!
Et tu, Steve?
What just happened?
You've made
the right choice, son
Sentinels! Keep them safe
Butter
Young Lockwood
we're getting close
I feel it in my beard!
Water goes in the top
and food comes out the bottom
It's gotta be inside that
big rock candy mountain!
This is exactly why I wanted you
on this mission
Sally forth, Lockwood
I can't believe Flint
is still listening to that guy!
Flint is naive It appears
he is being manipulated
for some nefarious purpose
Of course he is!
Sam! Freeze!
What?
Stay calm and walk toward me
slowly
Very slowly
Oh, come on
Now you're acting weird
I'm in no mood for this
Stop right there, cheese monster!
Nobody eats my friends
on my watch!
No, wait! Chester's been lying to us about
these creatures, and I am going to prove it
Sam, don't do it!
It's foodicide!
Danger! Danger! Danger!
Nice cheespider
Yellow Dude!
You got specialsauced!
Its Okay, guys See?
She's not mean She's just
a little beefy
What's it doing?
I think she wants you
to scratch her buns
I like that too
Who's a good cheespider?
She's cute!
But why did she attack us before?
Because we were dressed
like them
She doesn't like backpacks?
No It appears she
doesn't like Live Corp
The food creatures know something
we do not
Gasp!
Who's Evel?
Not "Evel" Evil
I knew it! Chester's
up to something terrible
We have to warn Flint!
Let's ride!
Run!
You're not warning
anyone about anything
Oh, crap balls
Magnificent
The FLDSMDFR
must be up there
A very unpleasant fall
Finish the job, Lockwood
Yes, sir
Made it!
FLDSMDFR
Look, I'm sorry I have to
do this to you
again
But I can't let your swimming
cheespiders destroy Lady Liberty
or the world
Marshmallow
They're like
a family
Sam was right
This is a mistake
Oh, dear!
Sir! Sir?
There it is
Wait In all its glory
Chester, look, I can't do this
Oh, okay I will
What? Wait
Chester, wait We can't destroy it
Let go of me, Lockwood
No, sir, I can't let you do this
No! No! No!
Live Corp
The BS-USB
reprogrammed it?
It was never gonna
turn off the machine
A BS-USB? Hello
Your machine is what I wanted
all along
You lied to me
Of course I lied to you
I knew you'd eventually fall
for these pathetic creatures
But you were my idol
My whole life, I looked up to you
I wanted to be you!
Oh, Lockwood I was just using you
to get your invention
We're ready
Launch Operation Slice and Dice
And now that I've got what I want,
I no longer need you
I'm afraid we're going to have to
let you go
Wait, wait, wait No, no, please
That's not natural
No, no, no
Easy, easy, you guys Don't cry
Okay, Steve If me and you put
our two brilliant minds together
we will get out of here
Steve?
Brent, do you ever get
the feeling that maybe Steve Lockwood
is just a monkey?
Why would you say that
about him, Earl?
Why would you ever say that?
Of course he's just a monkey
How stupid are you people?
No one should ever put
any trust in a monkey
Chester thinks you're a monkey
Well, I'm an ape Chester knows that
But he calls you a monkey
It is true, he does
He's just joking around
Chester's my best friend
If Chester was really your friend
would he still call you a monkey?
Nwoo! Nwoo!
Flint
Dad
What's happening, son?
You look terrible
What's with all of them?
They saved my life
I let Chester steal the machine and now
he's starting Operation Slice and Dice
Come on, son You're really
not making any sense
Look, Chester's gonna wipe out
all the foodimals
My friends tried to tell me they
were good, but I didn't listen
Everything I touch just gets ruined
Nwoo!
Barry?
Barry I'm so sorry I misjudged you
I should have listened to Sam
Saspa Sam
What is it? What are you trying to say?
Saspa, Saspa
Saspa!
Saspa
Sassy pants Dad
Saspa, Saspa!
Sam and the gang?
It looks like a Sentinel of Safety
Sassy pants
Sassy pants? No, Dad He's saying
Sentinels captured Sam and the gang
And they're being held in the factory?
We gotta get them out of there
But how? There's just two of us
Nwoo!
Nwoo! Nwoo!
Hey, what's with all the "Nwoos"?
Why do they have my TV?
Water goes in the top
and food comes out the bottom
Nwoo! Nwoo!
What's it, broken or something?
What's it doing?
Nwoo!
Here, you take it, you take it
Nwoo
It's saying that I'm Nwoo Nwoo
Nwoo Nwoo
Nwoo
Look, Flint, they came here to help
We all did It's time to let us
Okay, I don't know
if you can understand me
I know you think I'm Nwoo
But the truth is I'm no Nwoo
I'm just a man
A man who's made a lot of mistakes
in the last couple of days
And now my friends are in
a lot of trouble, thanks to me
Someone once told me
that I didn't need friends
That I could accomplish more
by myself
I know now more than ever
that he was wrong
We need all the friends we can get
And I need your help
All of you Fruits
vegetables and meat!
I need you to help me
to get into that
factory, save our friends
and get our home back!
Okay, now I just gotta figure out
how to get in there
With the right rod and tackle,
I could cast you up
into that unfinished part
of the factory
Should be a piece of cake
Dad, let's go fishing
Wildebeets!
Meatballrus! Go, go, go!
Watermelophant, do your thing!
Spray On Shoes
Hair Un Balder
Grocery Deliverator
Helmet
Got it
Ready when you are, Dad!
Ready, skipper, my boy
It's too heavy!
Here comes the cavalry
No way! Subs!
Subwhales!
Prepare to release lure
Hit it, Sweet
Catch the big one, buddy
Yes!
We have a problem
Nwoo, in here
What's going on?
Sam's backpack
They were here!
Good cheespider
Saspa?
Got it, Barry
Thanks, cheespider
Nwoo!
Barry, use the Grocery Deliverator
to save your friends
I'll go save mine
There's a leek in my boat
Flint!
Go, go, go!
Hey
freeze!
Food fight!
Crab cakes!
Run!
I'm all cheesed up
Retreat!
Head scan complete
Lockwood?
You're still alive?
That's right Hands up
Give me back my friends
Of course! I have them right here
Hey, Flint
Sam! Guys!
Chester, let them go!
Don't worry, Lockwood,
I'll let them go
Right into my supersized
Food Bar machine
Food Bars?
Food Bars? You're going to
turn them into Food Bars?
Yes, Food Bars
The lifeblood of my company
I learned your FLDSMDFR food
is far more delicious than "food" food
So using your foodimals
as ingredients
would make my products
superdelicious!
I had to have your invention
Unfortunately, I couldn't find it
Until you helped me
FLDSMDFR!
Watermelon!
You're a monster!
Those are living creatures
Yes, that's the problem
Food with legs
is much harder to catch
They hide, they fight back,
they want to live
But now that I control
your FLDSMDFR
I can pave your island
and work in complete secrecy
Live Corp will remain
the coolest, hippest company
in the world
with a new Food Bar version
80!
I never should have believed in you
Yes, that was quite foolish
Now if you want your friends back,
I suggest you drop your cans
Don't do it, Flint! Save the island!
But you are my island
Okay, first, shut up
Then drop the cans
or I drop your friends
Okay, okay There
Oh, no, Flint This is embarrassing
I changed my mind
Please understand
I can't leave any witnesses
Barb, grind them
But, sir, I didn't think we were going to
This is why I work alone
Monkey!
You are dismissed
And now, without
further ado
Flint, hurry!
Why won't this go faster?
Give me that controller!
Sure, come and get it
But which one of us has it?
Is it me?
Or me?
Earl, can't you break
us out of here?
Yellow police tape!
The one thing I can't break
Forkenknifenspooninator!
Sam, guys, listen
Invisible coffee table!
I'm sorry I was such an idiot
Flint, that's true but
now may not be the time!
Please let me finish
I took you all for granted
I should have listened to you
Okay, go on But hurry!
The truth is I need each
and every one of you guys
You're more than my friends
You're my family
How sweet Note to self:
put that on their tombstones
Good one, Chester!
Don't you see, young Lockwood?
These friends are the reason
you keep losing
Well, it's better than ending up
alone like you
I'm not alone!
I've got holograms!
Flint! Why don't you throw him
a party?
We love parties
Party?
Party!
Party's over, Lockwood
No!
Not yet
I think it's time to celebrate!
No!
Celebrate!
Yes!
Thanks, lab partner Helping!
Guys, I'm
so sorry for being such a Chester!
Okay, I guess I deserve that
No, Flint! Chester!
I've got what I want
Enjoy your friends, Lockwood
No! No!
Don't do this!
Food!
Anybody gonna be keeping
folks safe in this town, it's me
Tacodile supreme
It's over, Chester
Mustache!
Now hand over the FLDSMDFR
No! Never!
Chester
there's nowhere to go
That's what you think
Save me, monkey!
Rm an ape!
Bad monkey! Give that back!
Bad monk!
My holograms! Save me!
We're here for you
You're going to be fine
We'll save you
You see, Flint?
With my holograms
Oh, fudge
I saved myself
That will leave a bad taste
in your mouth
I believe this belongs to you
Here you go, Pal
Gosh, I hope this works
Pickle
Cheeseburger
Leek Strawberry Lemon
Yes!
Banana
It's enough to make a grown man cry
And that's okay
You go right ahead, tear
Guys, do you think we could
still work together?
I think we will work great together
Come on, bring it on in, Barb
This is nice
Ape!
Monkey
I'm proud of you, son
Thanks, Dad
But there's one last thing
I need to do
Okay, now, son
Now, once you put it on like that
all you have to do is cast it
So like this?
No, no, no
Here, let me show you how
See, it's all in the wrist Like this
Catch the big one, boy
Am I fishing?
Yup
I'm fishing!
You've got a live one
Now reel him in, Flint
That's it Steady, steady
He's a fighter!
I got one!
I got one, Dad!
Okay
Can we do this again?
Like all the time?
You betcha, skipper
Sam, guys, I caught my first fish!
Way to go, Flint!
Flint Lockwood, you are a fisherman
Happy
Hey, look, rainbows!
Strawberry
Hi, Steve
Hello, Steven I'm Barb
So do you wanna
go get coffee sometime?
Dinner!
Even better!
subtitled by  SELVAHEMA