This is Berk...
the best-kept secret
this side of, well, anywhere.
Granted, it may not look like much,
but this wet heap of rock...
packs more than a few surprises.
Life here is amazing,
just not for the faint of heart.
You see, where most folks enjoy hobbies
like whittling or needlepoint...
we Berkians prefer...
a little something we like to call...
dragon racing!
I'm sorry, Fishlegs. Did you want that?
Snotlout, that was mine!
Here you go, babe.
Did I tell you
that you look amazing today...
because you do.
Come on, Barf.
It's starting to stink around here.
Nope. Still hates you.
Let's blow this place, Belch!
All right!
Yeah!
That's nine for the Twins...
Astrid lags with three.
Fishlegs and Snotlout trail with none.
And Hiccup is...
nowhere to be found.
Scared him off with the big talk,
didn't you, Stoick?
What are you doing, Snotlout?
They're gonna win now.
She's my princess.
Whatever she wants, she gets.
Ruffnut?
Didn't she try to bury you alive?
Only for a few hours.
Now, dragons used to be
a bit of a problem here...
but that was 5 years ago.
Now, they have all moved in.
And really, why wouldn't they?
We have custom stables...
all-you-can-eat feeding stations...
a full-service dragon wash...
even top-of-the-line fire prevention
if I do say so myself.
It's time, Gobber.
Righty-ho. Last lap!
The Black Sheep!
Come on, Stormfly.
We can still win this thing!
Come on, Barf!
Let's go!
Go, Meatlug!
Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
This is your big moment.
Have a nice flight!
Up, up, up!
No!
Yes!
Good job, Meatlug.
Here you go, darling.
Mine is worth ten.
Yeah! The Black Sheep!
You guys are fighting for Ruffnut?
I'm totally winning!
We're winning together!
No!
No one can stop me now!
Except for me.
We're attached, genius.
Quit trying to steal all my glory!
Hey!
Get them, Astrid!
It's my glory!
Always ruining everything!
No sheep, no glory!
Gotcha!
Astrid!
Well played!
That's my future daughter-in-law!
Excuse me.
Stormfly!
That's 1 3! Astrid takes the game!
Yep, Berk is pretty much perfect.
All of my hard work has paid off.
And it's a good thing, too, because
with Vikings on the backs of dragons...
the world just got a whole lot bigger.
Yeah!
So what do you think, bud?
You wanna give this another shot?
Toothless! Lt will be fine.
Ready?
Yeah!
This is amazing!
No longer amazing!
Toothless!
Oh, no!
That really came out of nowhere.
We have to work
on your solo gliding there, bud.
That locked-up tail...
makes for some
pretty sloppy rescue maneuvers, hey?
Looks like we found another one, bud.
What, do you want an apology?
Is that why you're pouting,
big baby boo?
Well, try this on!
You feeling it yet?
Picking up on all of my
heartfelt remorse?
Come on, come on.
You wouldn't hurt a one-legged...
You're right! You're right!
You win. You win.
He's down. And it's ugly.
Dragons and Vikings, enemies again...
locked in combat to the bitter...
You know that doesn't wash out.
So, what should we name it?
Itchy Armpit it is.
What do you reckon, bud?
Think we might find a few
Timberjacks in those woods?
The odd Whispering Death or two
in the rocks?
Who knows? Maybe we'll finally
track down another Night Fury.
Wouldn't that be something?
So, what do you say?
Just keep going?
Afternoon, milady.
Where have you been?
Hi.
Winning races, what else?
The real question is...
where have you been?
Avoiding my dad.
Oh, no. What happened now?
You're gonna love this.
I wake up. The sun is shining.
Terrible Terrors
are singing on the rooftop.
I saunter down to breakfast...
thinking all is right with the world
and I get...
Son, we need to talk.
Not now, Dad. I got a whole day
of goofing off to get started.
Okay, first of all,
I don't sound like that.
Who is this character?
And second, what is that thing
you're doing with my shoulders?
Yeah, that's a truly flattering
impersonation.
Anyway, he goes...
You're the pride of Berk, son,
and I couldn't be prouder.
Aw, thanks, Dad.
I'm pretty impressed with myself, too.
When have I ever
done that with my hands?
You just did.
Okay. Just hold still.
This is very serious.
You're all grown up...
and since no chief could ask
for a better successor...
I've decided...
To make you chief!
Oh, my gods! Hiccup, that's amazing!
You're gonna wear out the spring coil.
The calibration is very sensitive.
Yeah...
so this is what I'm dealing with.
What did you tell him?
I didn't. By the time he turned around,
I was gone.
It's a lot of responsibility.
The map will have to wait for sure...
and I'll need to fly Toothless,
since you'll be too busy, but...
It's not me, Astrid.
All those speeches and planning,
and running the village, that's his thing.
I think you're missing the point.
I mean, chief. What an honor.
I'd be pretty excited.
I'm not like you.
You know exactly who you are.
You always have.
But I'm still looking.
I know that I'm not my father...
and I never met my mother...
so what does that make me?
What you're searching for
isn't out there, Hiccup.
It's in here.
Maybe you just don't see it yet.
Maybe.
But you know...
there is something out there.
Hiccup...
Stay close.
What happened here?
All right, easy, bud.
Hiccup!
Fire!
Astrid, look out!
Hiccup!
Watch the tail!
Tie those legs up!
Is that what I think it is?
Stop!
Stormfly!
What are you doing?
Back again?
Soil my britches.
That is a Night Fury.
I thought they were all gone for good.
It looks like our luck's had a turn
for the better, lads.
Don't think Drago has one of those...
in his dragon army.
Dragon army?
Look, we don't want any trouble.
You should have thought of that
before you stole all of our dragons...
and blasted our fort to bits!
What are you talking about?
You think we did this?
Dragon trapping is hard enough work as
it is without do-gooder dragon riders...
sneaking in to rescue them.
What do-gooder?
There are other dragon riders?
You mean other than your thieving friend
from last night? You tell me.
You may have an ice-spitting dragon
on your side...
but we still have a quota to fill.
How do you suppose
we explain this mess to Drago Bludvist?
Drago what-fist?
Does anything you say make sense?
He's expecting a new shipment of dragons
for his army by tomorrow.
And Drago don't take well to excuses.
This is what he gave me...
last time I showed up empty-handed.
He promised to be far less understanding
in the future.
All right, look, we don't know anything
about a dragon thief...
or an ice-spitting dragon...
or your lunatic boss
and his dragon army, okay?
Just give us back our dragon
and we'll go...
strange, hostile person
whom we've never met.
Where are my manners?
I'm Eret...
son of Eret.
Finest dragon trapper alive.
After all...
it's not just anyone
who can capture a Night Fury.
And this is Toothless.
He says we're going. Now.
They all say that.
Rush 'em, lads!
Stormfly! Come on!
Go! Go!
You will never
hold on to those dragons...
you hear me?
Drago is coming for them all!
Come on, Meatlug!
Hey, there, Stoick!
Hey, how are you? Beautiful day.
Hello, Spitelout. Great race.
Sorry, Mrs. Ack.
Any sign of him?
He's probably flown off the
edge of the world by now.
Are you sure you want that kid
running the village?
You can still delay your retirement.
He's ready. You'll see.
There he is!
The pride of Berk!
Who finally decided
to show up for work. Yay.
Sorry. Got held up.
Dad, could I have a word?
Something you're itching to tell me?
Not quite the itch
you're thinking of, but yes.
Good man! Now, lesson one.
A chief's first duty is to his people,
so... 41?
Can we just talk in private?
Forty...
That's me! That's me! I'm next!
If we could just talk...
Excuse me. I have been here all day.
Okay, okay.
I want one of those high seaters...
with lots of spikes
and a big stowage compartment.
Absolutely. You got it, sir.
Dad, this is actually a little more
important than building saddles.
Lesson two. No task is too small
when it comes to serving your people.
Excuse us, Grump.
Dad, can we just talk...
Grump!
You let the forge die down again!
That's it, Grump.
You're going up for adoption.
There you go. Go on. Have away.
Seriously, I really need to tell you
about this new land we came across.
Another one?
Any new dragons?
We didn't stick around to find out.
These folks weren't particularly friendly.
Really? Your Night Fury and Deadly Nadder
didn't bring them cheering to the rooftops?
No, this was different.
Not the standard run-for-the-hills
hoo-ha I've come to enjoy.
These guys were trappers.
Dragon trappers.
You should have seen their fort.
All blown apart and stuck in giant
spikes of ice. Lt was weird!
I've never seen anything like it.
And worst of all, they thought we did it!
You two are gonna get yourselves
in serious trouble one of these days.
Not everyone
appreciates this way of life.
Aye, Gobber's right, son.
Best we keep to our own.
Besides, you'll have
more important uses for your time.
Once we make the big announcement!
They are building a dragon army.
Or at least the guy they work for is.
Dargo Bloody Fist, or something.
I'll bloody his fist with my face
if he tries to take my dragon!
Or mine!
You're such a moron.
A beautiful moron.
Yeah.
Bludvist? Drago Bludvist?
Yeah. Wait.
You know him?
Ground all dragons!
What? Why?
Seal the gates!
Lower the storm doors!
Wait! What is happening?
Come on!
You heard the man! Lock it down.
No dragon or Viking sets foot
off this island until I give the word!
Wait, because some guy you knew
is stirring up trouble...
in some faraway land?
Because Drago Bludvist is a madman...
without conscience or mercy.
And if he's built a dragon army,
gods help us all.
Get them into their pens! Quickly!
Then, let's ride back out there.
We'll follow those trappers to Drago
and talk some sense into him.
No. We fortify the island.
It's our duty to keep the peace!
Peace is over, Hiccup.
I must prepare you for war.
War?
Dad, if Drago is coming for our dragons...
we can't wait around for him to get here.
Let's go find him and change his mind.
No, some minds won't be changed, Hiccup.
Berk is what you need to worry about.
A chief protects his own.
Secure the stables!
Latch every stall!
Hiccup, don't!
I have to.
This way!
Quickly!
Hiccup!
Come on!
Keep your eyes peeled, lads!
With this wind,
we'll reach Drago by daybreak...
so best we fill this ship up
with dragons, and quick!
It's no time to be picky.
Eret?
Not if we want to keep our...
heads! Off the port quarter!
Net them, lads!
Take them down!
You're not getting away this time.
Fire!
Reload!
Reload! Incoming!
And here I was...
worried we might turn up empty-handed.
Nope. It's your lucky day.
We give up.
That's one Night Fury,
one Deadly Nadder...
and two of the finest dragon riders
west of Luk Tuk.
That ought to make the boss happy, right?
Excuse us.
What are you doing?
Toothless, stay.
The dragons don't care for cramped spaces,
so they'll just hang out with you.
They won't be any trouble.
Unless you do that.
You know, wooden boat, big ocean.
How is your swimming?
Not good.
Almost forgot.
You can't have armed prisoners.
How is this a plan?
Just what every dragon trapper needs.
One end coats the blade
in Monstrous Nightmare saliva.
The other sprays Hideous Zippleback gas.
All it takes is a spark, and...
Yeah, there you go.
Once they see you as one of their own...
even the testiest dragons can be trained.
Right, bud?
Give me that!
What game are you playing?
No game. We just wanna meet Drago.
Why?
Because I'm going to change his mind
about dragons.
He can be really persuasive.
Once you've earned his loyalty...
there is nothing
a dragon won't do for you.
You won't be changing
any minds around here.
I can change yours.
Right here. Right now.
May I?
Dragon riders!
Put me down!
Snotlout, what are you doing?
See how well I protect and provide?
What is with all the nets?
Hey, watch it! That was...
close.
Oh, my.
Me likey.
Take me.
Hold your fire!
What are you guys doing here?
We're here to rescue you!
I don't need to be rescued!
Enough!
Well, didn't you just
pick the wrong ship?
I am Eret, son of Eret.
Get this thing off me.
Anyone else?
That's what I figured.
You, saddle up. We're going home.
No.
Of all the irresponsible...
I'm trying to protect our dragons
and stop a war!
How is that irresponsible?
Because war is what he wants, son!
Years ago, there was
a great gathering of chieftains...
to discuss the dragon scourge
we all faced.
Into our midst
came a stranger from a strange land...
covered in scars
and draped in a cloak of dragon skin.
He carried no weapon...
and spoke softly,
saying that he...
Drago Bludvist,
was a man of the people...
devoted to freeing mankind
from the tyranny of dragons.
He claimed that he alone
could control the dragons...
and that he alone could keep us safe...
if we chose to bow down...
and follow him.
Stupid.
Good one.
Aye, we laughed, too.
Until he wrapped himself in his cloak
and cried out...
Then see how well you do without me!
The rooftop suddenly burst into flames...
and from it, armored dragons descended...
burning the hall to the ground.
I was the only one to escape.
Men who kill without reason
cannot be reasoned with.
Maybe.
Hiccup!
I'm still going to try.
This is what I'm good at.
And if I could change your mind...
I can change his, too.
Come on.
Let's go.
No!
Lead the others back to Berk.
I've had enough mutiny for one day.
I like that.
Ruffnut!
Okay!
Don't worry, bud.
I'm not gonna let anything happen to you.
I promise.
Come on, Dad!
Really?
Okay.
No sudden moves.
Hold on. Hold on.
Toothless!
Hey! You left my dragon back there!
He can't fly on his own! He will drown!
Hey!
We have to head back for my dragon!
Who are you?
The dragon thief?
Drago Bludvist?
Do you even understand what I'm saying?
Toothless!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
I'm glad to see you, too, bud.
You really had me worried, there.
Hiccup?
Could it be?
After all these years?
How is this possible?
Should I know you?
No, you were only a babe.
But a mother never forgets.
Come.
Boar-headed! Just like his mother!
Aye, she could never stay put either.
He's just twenty.
And a Viking.
Could there be a worse combination?
When I think of how stubborn
and senseless you were back in the day...
Well, not much has changed, actually.
You know what he's like.
He won't give up, Gobber.
And if Hiccup finds Drago,
before we find him...
Nothing can hurt Hiccup...
so long as that Night Fury's around.
It's a Night Fury!
Find them, Skullcrusher.
Find them.
Hold on. Wait just a minute.
This way!
Come back here!
Come.
You can't just say something like that
and run off!
You're my mother?
I mean, what the...
Do you grasp how insane it sounds?
Come, quickly!
I have questions!
Where have you been all this time?
What have you been doing?
But they said you were dead!
Everyone thinks you were eaten by...
This is where you've been
for 20 years?
You've been rescuing them.
Unbelievable.
You're not upset?
What? No.
I don't know.
It's a bit much to get my
head around, to be frank.
It's not every day you find out...
your mother is some kind of crazy,
feral, vigilante dragon lady.
At least I'm not boring, right?
I suppose
there is that one specific thing.
Do you like it?
I don't have the words.
Can I...
He's beautiful.
Incredible!
He might very well
be the last of his kind.
And look, he's your age.
Wow.
No wonder you get along so well.
And retractable teeth!
How did you manage to...
I found him in the woods.
He was shot down and wounded.
This Snafflefang lost his leg
to one of Drago Bludvist's iron traps.
This Raincutter had her wing sliced
by razor netting.
And this poor Hobblegrunt...
was blinded by a tree snare...
and then left to die alone and scared.
And what of this?
Did Drago or his trappers do this, too?
Yeah...
The crazy thing is...
I'm actually the one who shot him down.
Hey, it's okay, though.
He got me back!
Right, bud?
You couldn't save all of me, could you?
You just had to make it even.
So, peg leg!
What did your father think
of your Night Fury friend?
He didn't take it all that well.
But then he changed.
They all did.
Pretty soon, everyone back
home had dragons of their own.
If only it were possible.
No, really.
Believe me, I tried, as well...
but people are not
capable of change, Hiccup.
Some of us were just born different.
Hoist the torches!
Berk was a land of kill-or-be-killed...
but I believed peace was possible.
Stop! You'll only make it worse!
It was a very unpopular opinion.
Hiccup!
Then, one night,
a dragon broke into our house...
finding you in the cradle.
I rushed to protect you.
But what I saw...
was proof of everything I believed.
This wasn't a vicious beast...
but an intelligent, gentle creature...
whose soul...
reflected my own.
Valka, run!
No! Don't!
Hold on!
No! Stoick!
Valka!
Stoick!
Valka.
You and your father
nearly died that night...
all because I couldn't kill a dragon.
It runs in the family.
It broke my heart to stay away...
but I believed
you would be safer if I did.
How did you survive?
Cloudjumper never meant to harm me.
He must have thought
I belonged here.
In the home of the great Bewilderbeast.
The alpha species.
One of the very few that still exist.
Every nest has its queen...
but this is the king of all dragons.
With his icy breath,
this graceful giant built our nest.
A safe haven for dragons everywhere.
Wait, that's the ice-spitter?
He's responsible for all that destruction?
He protects us.
We all live under his care
and his command.
All but the babies, of course...
who listen to no one!
I've lived among them...
for 20 years, Hiccup...
discovering their secrets.
He likes you.
Wow.
You must be hungry.
Yeah, I could eat.
Good. It's feeding time.
I don't like it.
They should have been back
with Hiccup by now.
I don't like it either.
Eret, son of Eret...
was the man of my dreams. My everything!
But, baby, I grew facial hair for you.
Me, too.
What if Drago shot them down?
What if they need our help?
We have to find them.
Wait, what?
No, but Stoick said...
Lt doesn't matter what he said,
if they have all been captured.
Come on!
Do we go back?
We have nowhere to go,
nothing to sell...
and no heads to call our own!
If we don't turn up with dragons,
and fast...
Careful what you wish for!
Eret, son of Eret!
What is this?
A kidnapping.
Yay! Can he ride with me?
Can he? Can he?
You're gonna show us the way to Drago.
And help dragon riders sneak
into Drago's camp? Just kill me now.
That could be arranged.
Stormfly, drop it!
Good girl!
Stormfly, fetch!
All right!
Okay! I'll take you to Drago!
Works every time.
Hey, I thought we were going to eat.
We are.
Then, from Dragon Island...
I found this archipelago.
There.
When I'm up here...
I don't even feel the cold. I just feel...
Free.
This is what it is to be a dragon, Hiccup.
It's all well and good
to call yourself a dragon...
but can you fly?
Oh, no!
Man! Almost!
We just about had it that time!
Incredible.
Well, not bad yourself.
All this time, you took after me.
And where was I?
I'm so sorry, Hiccup.
Can we start over?
Will you give me another chance?
I can teach you all that I have learned
these past 20 years.
Like...
Wow.
Now you can make those tight turns.
Did you know about this?
Every dragon has its secrets.
And I'll show them all to you.
We'll unlock every mystery...
find every last
species together...
as mother and son.
This gift we share, Hiccup, it bonds us.
This is who you are, son.
Who we are.
We will change the world
for all dragons.
We will make it a better, safer place.
Yeah.
That sounds amazing.
This is so great!
Now you and I can
go talk to Drago together.
What?
There's no talking to Drago.
But we have to...
No.
We must protect our own.
Come on, we should be getting back.
Okay! Look, I got you here.
Now get this thing off me.
Never take a toy from a dragon.
Don't you know anything?
Why does this keep happening to me?
What's down there?
Large diameter bubbles, massive lungs...
cold water deep dweller.
I'm thinking class five leviathan,
maybe six.
Meatlug! What's wrong, girl?
Drago!
Get off me!
Always great to see you, my friend!
Keeping warm up here?
As you can see, I'm right on time
with a new batch of dragons...
just like I promised.
He's waking up!
Give me some backup, here!
Drop the ropes!
Hookfang!
Hey!
What are you doing?
You belong to me now.
And as an added bonus...
I also caught you their riders.
No extra charge.
What?
Are you kidding me?
But you were so perfect!
Turns out, there is a whole
bunch of them out there.
How many?
Drago doesn't have them after all.
Hundreds.
A whole island full!
I wouldn't worry about it.
My men are hunting them down
as we speak.
They won't know where you're hiding,
I promise you that.
Yes, they will.
They know we're missing...
and they have tracking dragons.
If you so much as touch us,
Hiccup is gonna kick...
Hiccup?
He's not a problem.
Really. Trust me.
He's only the son of Stoick the Vast,
his heir to the throne of Berk...
and the greatest dragon master
this world has ever seen!
Dragon master?
I alone control the dragons!
No.
Sorry.
And unless you let us go, right now...
he will blast through here
on his Night Fury...
and blow your entire fleet of ships
to splinters.
Then they will be crying like babies.
Funny and beautiful.
Good one, babe!
Like babies, they always cry.
Real tiny ones.
First, there was one rider,
and now, all of Berk.
And you led them to me!
Drago!
Stop all preparations!
We must attack the dragon riders' nest
at once!
We will take down their alpha!
Then we will take Berk!
Drago.
And get rid of him.
Drago, please, I...
Stormfly!
No!
Well, bud, we can't wait around
for Drago to attack this place.
We've gotta find him first.
Let's go.
Easy now.
Are you kidding me?
How did you get in here?
The same way we are getting you out.
We?
All clear.
Toothless, come.
Wait. There's something
you need to know.
Yeah, yeah, tell me on the way.
This isn't an on-the-way
kind of update, actually.
I've heard enough.
More of the
earth-shattering-development variety.
Yeah, just add it to the pile.
Dad, unlike most surprises I spring on you,
this is one you'll like.
I promise.
You just have to handle it delicately.
You might want to take this one.
Oh, boy.
Dad...
could you put the sword away, please?
I know what you're gonna say, Stoick.
How could I have done this?
Stayed away all of these years?
And why did I not come back to you?
To our son?
What sign did I have
that you could change, Stoick?
That anyone on Berk could?
I pleaded so many times
to stop the fighting...
to find another answer,
but did any of you listen?
This is why I never married.
This and one other reason.
I know that I left you
to raise Hiccup alone...
but I thought
he would be better off without me.
And I was wrong, I see that now, but...
Stop being so stoic, Stoick!
Go on.
Shout, scream, say something!
You're as beautiful
as the day I lost you.
Could this day get any worse?
Let me see.
We're gonna jump into freezing cold water,
and then die from drowning.
Looks refreshing.
Please, ladies first.
You are a steaming heap of dragon...
Duck.
Warn the others!
Get them, you son of an Eret.
Take that!
Okay, I love you again.
Pathetic. You can still jump.
So, are we going to save your dragons
and get out of here, or not?
Check every trap.
They're here somewhere.
Meatlug?
Anyone coming?
I don't know.
You just keep doing what you are doing.
Keep cranking.
Thank you for saving my life.
Now let me return the favor.
Mom, you'd never even recognize it.
Where we used to make weapons,
we now build saddles, wing-slings.
We even fix dragon teeth!
You wouldn't believe how much
everything's changed.
Our son has changed Berk for the better.
I think we did well
with this one, Val.
Thanks, Dad.
I'm a little out of practice.
Well, you know...
I didn't marry you for your cooking.
I hope not.
Her meatballs could kill
more beasts than a battle-axe.
I've still got a few
knocking around in here.
And once you move back in,
with all your dragons...
Drago won't even stand a chance.
Everything will be okay!
Slow down, son.
It's a lot to take in.
Gotcha.
I love this one.
Remember our song, Val?
I'll swim and sail on savage seas
With ne'er a fear of drowning
And gladly ride the waves of life
If you will marry me
No scorching sun
Nor freezing cold Will stop...
Will stop me on my journey
Sorry.
If you will promise me your heart
And love...
And love me for eternity
My dearest one
My darling dear
Your mighty words astound me
But I've no need of mighty deeds
When I feel your arms around me
But I would bring you rings of gold
I'd even sing you poetry
Oh, would you?
And I would keep you from all harm
If you would stay beside me
I have no use for rings of gold
I care not for your poetry
I only want your hand to hold
I only want you near me
To love and kiss, to sweetly hold
For the dancing and the dreaming
Through all life's sorrows and delights
I'll keep your love inside me
I will swim and sail on savage seas
With ne'er a fear of drowning
And gladly ride the waves of life
If you will marry me
I'm still going
Gobber!
I'm done.
I thought I would have to die
before we could have that dance again.
No need for drastic measures.
For you, my dear...
anything.
Will you come home, Val?
Will you be my wife once again?
We can be a family!
What do you say?
Yes.
Great! I'll do the cooking.
Thank Odin you didn't listen to me, son.
We never would have found each other.
Toothless?
What's happening?
Oh, no.
Val?
Val! It's all right, it's all right.
We're a team now.
What do you want to do?
We have to save the dragons.
Aye. You got it!
Come on, son.
Whatever comes,
keep hitting the mountain.
We need to draw the alpha out.
Ready the traps!
Surprise!
Yeah!
What?
You really are full of surprises!
Let's go!
Dragon riders, coming through!
Fire!
Yeah!
Cut them down!
Eret, son of Eret!
Up, girl!
Lean left, Eret! That's it!
Look out!
Yeah, baby!
Take them down!
Heads up!
Dragon master.
Welcome aboard, dragon rider!
Thanks, I think.
Where have you been?
You know, catching up with Mom.
That's your mother?
Now you know
where I get my dramatic flair.
The alpha! Now we have a fight!
Come on, Toothless!
Show them what you got, bud.
That a boy!
I've waited a long time for this!
You cannot take our dragons!
They are controlled by the alpha!
Then it's a good thing
I brought a challenger.
Another one?
That is a class ten! Class ten!
No.
Come on! Take down the alpha!
Thank you.
For you, my dear...
anything.
Val, do you think you can stop them?
I'll do my best.
Come on, Cloudjumper!
You!
I watched you burn!
It takes more than a little fire
to kill me!
Stoick!
No!
We have won.
Now, finish her!
No!
Hold on!
Skullcrusher, go!
Come on, Gobber!
Right behind you, Stoick!
Stop!
This is the great dragon master?
The son of Stoick the Vast?
What shame he must feel.
All of this loss, and for what?
To become unstoppable?
To rule the world?
Dragons are kind, amazing creatures...
that can bring people together.
Or tear them apart.
You see...
I know what it is to live in fear.
To see my village burned...
my family taken.
But even as a boy...
left with nothing...
I vowed to rise above
the fear of dragons...
and liberate the people of this world.
Then why a dragon army?
You need dragons
to conquer other dragons.
Or maybe you need dragons
to conquer people.
To control those who follow you...
and to get rid of those who won't.
Clever boy.
The world wants peace.
And we have the answer back on Berk.
Just let me show you.
No!
Let me show you!
What in...
Hiccup!
Come on, Gobber!
Okay, change of plan!
No dragon can resist the alpha's command.
So, he who controls the alpha...
controls them all.
Toothless?
Toothless, you okay, bud?
What's going on?
Witness true strength.
The strength of will over others.
In the face of it...
you are nothing.
What did he just tell you?
Toothless, come on.
What's the matter with you?
No, no, no, no. Come on.
What are you doing? Knock it off.
Stop! Snap out of it!
Toothless, no!
Toothless!
Don't!
Hiccup!
Stop!
Son!
Dad!
No!
No.
Dad!
Stoick!
Dad.
No, you...
No.
No, no, no.
No! Get away from him!
Go on! Get out of here!
Get away!
It's not his fault.
You know that.
Good dragons...
under the control of bad people...
Wait! Don't go.
Do bad things.
Come on!
Gather the men and meet me at Berk!
Toothless!
No, don't.
May the Valkyries welcome you...
and lead you through
Odin's great battlefield.
May they sing your name
with love and fury...
so that we might hear it rise
from the depths of Valhalla...
and know that you have taken
your rightful place...
at the table of kings.
For a great man has fallen.
A warrior. A chieftain.
A father.
A friend.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm not the chief
that you wanted me to be.
And I'm not the peacekeeper
I thought I was.
I don't know...
You came early into this world.
You were such a wee thing.
So frail, so fragile.
I feared you wouldn't make it.
But your father...
he never doubted.
He always said you would become
the strongest of them all.
And he was right.
You have the heart of a chief
and a soul of a dragon.
Only you can bring our worlds together.
That is who you are, son.
I was so afraid of becoming my dad.
Mostly because I thought I never could.
How do you become someone that great?
That brave? That selfless?
I guess you can only try.
A chief protects his own.
We are going back.
With what?
He took all the dragons.
Not all of them.
I don't want to die!
We can't fly these things!
Yeah, no kidding!
But won't that Bewilderbeast just
take control of these guys, too?
They're babies.
They don't listen to anyone.
Yeah! Just like us!
This is very dangerous!
Some might suggest
this is poorly conceived.
It's a good thing that I never listen.
So what is your plan?
Get Toothless back and kick Drago's...
Heads up!
And that thing.
That's a good boy.
Watch the furniture!
Where are you going?
Your chief is dead.
Stoick?
No one can protect you now.
No.
He took all the dragons!
Distract the alpha.
Try to keep his focus off Toothless.
How?
Have you forgotten
who you're riding with?
There isn't a dragon alive
that I can't wrangle!
Except for this one!
Amateur.
Hey, look. It's Hiccup!
What?
Keep them coming!
Black sheep, baby!
Ten points!
Oh-oh.
I'm okay!
You certainly are hard to get rid of,
I'll say that.
Toothless?
Hey...
it's me, bud.
It's me.
It's me. I'm right here, bud.
Come back to me.
He's not yours anymore.
He belongs to the alpha.
But, please, great dragon master...
try to take him.
He will not miss a second time.
It wasn't your fault, bud.
They made you do it.
You would never hurt him.
You would never hurt me.
How are you doing that?
Please. You are my best friend, bud.
My best friend.
Atta boy! That's it!
I'm here!
Enough!
Hang on!
Almost there, buddy.
Do something!
We need to get those two apart.
We have to block him out, Toothless.
Do you trust me, bud?
We can do this.
You and me.
As one.
That's it.
Now let's try this one more time!
Take him down, babe!
Go get them!
Take control of it!
Shut it out, Toothless.
Stop them!
Now!
Not again.
Toothless! It's now or never!
Come on, bud!
Hold on!
Yeah! We did it!
Hold him there, Toothless.
It's all over now.
Or is it?
Oh, no!
No!
Hiccup!
He's challenging the alpha!
To protect you.
No, no, no! No!
Fight back! Fight!
Fight!
What's the matter with you?
Now do you get it?
This is what it is
to earn a dragon's loyalty.
Let this end. Now.
Never!
Come on!
Fight!
The alpha protects them all.
You never cease to amaze me, bud.
Thank you.
Toothless, you know that doesn't wash out!
I knew you'd come back!
Stormfly!
Give me a cuddle, Grumpy!
Who's my little princess?
Don't you ever leave again, Hookfang.
You are! Yes, you are!
I missed you!
Oh, Barf!
Not you!
That was some pretty fine
dragon wrangling back there.
You'd make a good trapper.
You know, Skullcrusher's gonna need
somebody to look after him now.
Me?
I'd be honored.
Your father would be
every bit as proud as I am.
Thank you.
I'm really glad you're here, Mom.
And here I'll stay.
See?
I told you it was in here.
Still doing that one?
That's hilarious.
Come here, you.
The chief has come home!
Long live the chief! Long live the chief!
Long live the chief!
This is Berk.
A bit trampled and busted
and covered in ice...
but it's home.
It's our home.
Those who attacked us
are relentless and crazy.
But those who stopped them...
even more so!
We may be small in numbers...
but we stand for something...
bigger than anything
the world can pit against us.
We are the voice of peace.
And, bit by bit,
we will change this world.
You see, we have something they don't.
Sure, they have armies...
and they have armadas...
but we have...
our dragons!