Some people say
that fairies are the stuff of fantasy.
They think the world is just
what you can touch and hear and see,
while others say the tales and legends
cannot be dismissed.
They believe with all their hearts
that fairies truly do exist.
Throughout all time,
human beings and fairies never met,
till one very special summer
that we shall not soon forget.
Life is rising up
Surging forth in all directions
Every little buttercup
Is reaching out to find connections
Every blade of grass
Will touch the sunlight
The rain will touch the ground
Growing greener than it was before
Bees are droning by
Spider silk is softly spinning
Not a cloud in the sky
You know it's only the beginning
Every little blossom, every flower
Flings its petals wide
As the season comes round
Once more
Hey, Tink! You ready
for your first summer on the mainland?
Absolutely! It's so beautiful out here.
I can't believe we get to stay
for the whole season.
Well, what are we waiting for?
Race you down!
The breeze is blowing light and sweet
The grass, a carpet at your feet
Catch the colors
Feel the heat of the sun
All the sparrows in the dell
Swirling round like a carousel
Singing loud enough to tell everyone
Hi, guys.
Summer's just begun
There it is, Tink. Fairy camp!
All the winters, all the springs
Lead us here on fairy wings
A season of a thousand things
To be done
Summer's just begun
Hiya, Cheese!
- Did you have a nice flight?
- Incoming!
- Keep her level! Keep her level!
- Gear it down, Bobble!
- Smashing landing, Clanky.
- Thank you, Bobble.
Guys, I think you may
have over-packed.
- Come on, Tink. Let's go inside.
- Inside?
Tink, fairy camp isn't out here
in the open.
We need to stay hidden
from the humans.
- We do?
- Yeah.
That's why fairy camp is in here.
Cicadas, one at a time.
You, you and you. You, too.
Wow. It's like all of Pixie Hollow
under one tree!
Blaze!
Wow! The Queen Anne's lace
is looking beautiful.
- How are the looms working?
- Fine, thanks to you, Tink.
Next. Next. Next.
- How's the bee-liner working?
- Like a dream, Tink. Thanks.
- Great. Need any help with that wagon?
- No, thanks. She's running fine.
Okay. Glad to hear it.
Here's the first week's supply.
Okay, I'm off. I gotta go deliver
pixie dust to the other fairy camps,
but I'll see you in a couple clays.
And Tink! Don't worry.
You'll find something to fix.
I hope so.
In the meantime,
I need to go find some lost things.
Hold on, little miss spare parts.
You're not going near
the human house, are you?
- There's a human house?
- No! I mean, yes, but no.
- We stay away from humans.
- Iridessa!
- Tinker Bell knows that, don't you?
- Define "stay away. "
- It's gonna be a long summer.
- Grouchy.
- That's just Vidia being Vidia.
- No, the air. It smells grouchy.
- We might be in for a storm.
- Come on, Sil.
The sun is shining, the air is warm.
It's a beautiful day. Nothing's gonna...
Tinker Bell.
Thank goodness we're here, Father.
It's just like I remember it.
Well, of course, my darling.
Look at the creek and the woods
and the meadow!
I wish it was summer all year long!
Yes, Lizzy.
Tinker Bell, what are you doing here?
Vidia, this is amazing!
It's a carriage that moves by itself!
There's no horse. Seriously, look.
- Do you see a horse up there?
- No.
It's a horseless carriage!
And do you want to know how it works?
- Not really.
- So do I.
I think those wheels back there move
because this chain thing rotates.
And I think what rotates the chain
is this big...
I don't care, Tinker Bell. You shouldn't
be this close to the human house.
What if they see us?
Will you stop flitting around in there?
This is serious!
You know what, Vidia?
I think this powers the whole thing!
This, my dear, is exactly why tinkers
shouldn't come to the mainland. They...
Let me know if this does anything.
Well, anything? Vidia, you're all wet.
You don't say.
Father, Father, Father! Can we
bring our tea and scones outside
and have them here in the garden?
- It would be just like a little picnic.
- Not just now, Lizzy.
I still have to get the trunk unpacked
and the house settled.
Father, look!
What a magnificent butterfly.
My word. Absolutely astonishing.
It's so beautiful.
What kind of butterfly is it?
Well, judging from the epidermal
membrane, it's clearly an apatura iris,
but the wings
have two entirely different patterns.
Well, that's nearly impossible.
Well, I guess that's just the way
the fairies decided to paint it.
Lizzy, fairies do not paint
butterfly wings
because, as you know,
fairies are not real.
But of course they are.
The proof is right here.
- Their paint dripped all over its wing.
- Really, darling.
Rational people consider
a belief in fairies to be quite foolish.
- The wings are so fresh.
- What are you doing?
Its chrysalis must have been
in the meadow.
The meadow? Father, wait!
That's where I'm going.
Would you like to come?
Not now, Lizzy.
I have to update my field journal.
My interview at the museum
is tomorrow night.
You're going back already?
We just got here.
I know, sweetheart, and I'm very sorry.
But I'll only be gone for the day.
Mrs. Perkins will look after you,
and I'll be back in time to tuck you in.
- Promise?
- I promise.
- Okay.
- That's a good girl.
All clear!
Come on, Vidia.
- I can't fly. My wings are wet.
- That's right. Sorry.
Guess you'll have to walk back.
But don't worry, I'll keep you company.
Actually, it might be nice.
Or not.
So, I think I figured out the carriage.
Those bottles of goop
must keep it running smoothly,
like snail slime, you know?
Hate to see the size of the snail
that stuff comes from. And at first...
Here's your house, little fairies.
Wherever you are.
Just needs a little something more.
But I haven't quite figured out
what that sparky wire does.
Hey! Maybe the whole carriage
runs on lightning!
Are those wet wings still bugging you?
Here, Vidia, let me help you.
Tinker Bell, maybe if you spent
less time causing disasters,
you wouldn't have
to help everybody so much.
- The truth hurts, doesn't it?
- Look! We can use these back at camp!
Wow. These'll be perfect for the new
wagon prototype I've been working on.
Here. I bet if I took two or three
and tied them together,
I could make one really strong wheel!
It's a good thing we were walking
or we might never have seen these.
Vidia, where are your buttons?
Tinker Bell, I am not carrying
this human junk back to camp.
- Let's go!
Tinker Bell, we're not supposed
to go near human houses.
This isn't a human house.
They're a lot bigger.
Besides, the sign says,
"Fairies welcome. "
Who do you think wrote it? Humans!
Tinker Bell, you're not going in there.
Please tell me you're not going in there!
She went in there.
Wow.
Tinker Bell! Don't eat that!
This could be a trap.
Come on, Vidia. It's perfectly safe.
Really?
- Vidia.
- Not so safe now, is it?
Nice try, Vidia,
but you're not scaring me.
Gosh, this thing is amazing.
You just don't know when to stop,
do you?
Oh, no. Tink! Someone's coming!
The door is stuck!
Come on, Vidia.
You can do better than that.
- Tink!
- I wonder what this part does.
Tink! I'm serious! Get out of there!
Just a second. Just a second.
Vidia? Vidia?
Vidia, come on. Open the door.
You had your little...
Oh, no. What have I done?
Vidia? Okay, not funny anymore.
A fairy!
It's a real fairy!
Father! Father!
Father!
- Father! Father, Father!
- Yes, Lizzy.
You're never going to believe
what I found.
- Maybe later, Lizzy.
- But Father, Father, Father,
- Father, Father.
- Just a moment, dear.
- I'm very busy with my project.
- Yes, but Father!
- Father!
- Lizzy, please.
I must add this extraordinary discovery
to my field journal.
And here it is.
Is that the butterfly
we were looking at earlier?
Yes. Quite a specimen, isn't it?
You're not going to take it to London,
are you?
Yes, of course. The board of trustees
would never believe me
if they didn't see it themselves.
Now I'm sure to get that curatorship
at the museum.
Besides, as a member
of the scientific community,
I'm obligated to share significant
findings like this with my colleagues.
I know it's unfortunate for the specimen,
but really, there is no other way.
Now, dear.
What did you want me to see?
Never mind.
Where have you gone?
Mr. Twitches, no! Out! Out with you!
Mr. Twitches!
Bad cat! No, no, no!
Don't worry, little fairy.
Mr. Twitches won't bother you
as long as you're in there.
Naughty cat! You're going outside.
Tinker Bell's
been captured by humans!
- Oh, no.
- What happened? Is she okay?
- Is she all right?
- What's this? Tinker Bell?
- What happened, Vidia?
- Is she hurt?
Tinker Bell went into this little house
in the meadow and couldn't get out.
The door got jammed.
Then this human came from out
of nowhere and snatched her up,
but I know where she is.
We have to hurry and save her.
Then we better leave right away!
Sil, do you think the storm
will pass soon?
No, it looks like it's gonna get stronger.
Well, there's gotta be some way
to get to Tink.
We can't fly in the rain,
and the meadow's already flooded.
Maybe we don't have to fly.
If we get some big leaves and sew them
together with stem twine...
And miter-cut some twigs
for the sub-flooring.
Acorns as counterweights.
Some quick-dry maple sap
as reinforcement.
What are you two talking about?
- We're gonna build a boat!
- More mushroom caps, please!
- Here we go.
This one goes there.
That one goes there. Right?
Righty-o, Bobble.
- Right, more reeds over here.
- This thing had better work.
Give me the sap. You dip it in this way
and give it a big slap like so.
Come on. Come on. Let's get going.
There you go. Now you're talking!
It's working!
Well, this is it.
Hey, faith...
Trust...
- And pixie dust.
- Pixie dust.
Come on. Come on.
Hello.
You don't have to be scared.
I'm very nice.
You're so little.
Your dress is very leafy.
Did you make it yourself?
I like your wings.
They're like sparkly lace.
Your hair must be so soft.
Are you hungry? Maybe not.
That's okay.
I don't like some kinds of food, either.
I'm so sorry. Where are my manners?
There you go.
Wait! Wait! Wait! No, please!
I'm not going to hurt you!
Don't be afraid!
I just want to be your friend!
I really won't hurt you. I just love fairies.
I've been drawing fairies
all my life. See?
I drew that one when I was three,
but I did that green one last week.
I think it's much better.
I even started to paint
with the watercolors Father gave me.
Is it true that some fairies
paint butterfly wings?
I knew it!
These are some
of my favorite drawings.
This is a water fairy.
- You can tell because her skin is blue.
- Blue?
And here is a candy fairy
living in a lollipop tree.
Do all fairies live in trees
made of sweets?
Really? What about fairy circles?
Well, I hear
that if a person steps in one,
a fairy has to grant them three wishes
from their magic bag.
But if they don't,
they turn into a pile of delicious sugar,
- and then younger fairies...
- Wait. Wait a minute.
- ... must try and turn them back into...
- Where are you getting all this?
You jingle when you talk,
like a little bell!
So that's how fairies speak.
So what do you think of my fairies?
And my fairy house!
It got a little shaken up.
- Did you make this?
- I don't know what you're saying.
Did I make the fairy house? Yes, I did.
Do you like it?
The door's stuck.
Well, you're quite the little tinker,
aren't you?
What? Is that your name? Tinker?
Bell? Your name is Bell.
Tinker? Bell?
Tinker Bell? Tinker Bell.
What a lovely name!
Well, Tinker Bell, my name's Lizzy.
Do all fairies sound the same
when they talk?
How do you learn to be a fairy?
Do you go to fairy school?
Lizzy? Lizzy? Who are you talking to?
My fairy!
That's nice, dear. Now, I brought you
something I think you'll really enjoy.
These are some
of my old field journals.
Now, I picked out the ones
I thought would excite you the most.
This one on rocks and minerals
is particularly interesting.
- Is there a field journal about fairies?
- Of course not, Lizzy.
Books like this are based on fact
and scientific research,
which is quite the contrary
to your little figurines and drawings.
Well, just because you've never seen
a fairy doesn't mean they're not real.
Now, Lizzy, seeing is believing,
and without proof, it's just a fairy tale.
Now, here is a blank field journal.
Now, you're very talented, my darling,
and I'm sure you'll be able to fill it
with your own scientific research.
Yes, Father.
Now if only these leaks
were just pretend.
Tinker Bell, you can come out now.
Look, Lizzy, thanks for showing me
your collection, but I really should be...
You want to go?
I really wish you'd stay.
I'm sorry, Lizzy.
Okay, I understand.
So, I guess this is goodbye.
What's wrong?
Can't you fly in the rain?
You can stay with me
until the rain stops.
I'll show you around my room.
We can play with my toys.
We'll have so much fun.
- We're past the shallows!
- Aye! Drop the mainsail!
Dropping the mainsail!
- Trim the sail!
- Trimming the sail!
- Big thingy, dead ahead! Hard to port!
- Hard to port! Hard to port!
I recognize that wagon.
Stay on this course!
- Aye, Miss Vidia. Will do.
- I sure hope Tink is all right.
Who knows what terrible things
could be happening to her right now.
A fairy could get used to this.
Isn't it wonderful? Everything in this
house is just your size, Tinker Bell.
That's perfume. It smells like flowers.
My doll. She should be in bed by now.
How old are you? I'm nine.
Do you like my dollhouse?
Do fairies live in houses?
What are fairies' houses made of?
That's a cooker,
but it doesn't actually work.
What's your favorite food?
I mean, besides sweets?
I want to know all about real live fairies.
Perfect!
"Scientific fairy research. "
Okay. What's your favorite color?
Green is my favorite color, too!
I should start from the beginning.
Where do fairies come from?
I mean, where were you born?
Well, that one's
a little more complicated because...
So, a baby, when it laughs
for the first time...
A fairy...
Right. One second.
You were a funny-looking baby?
A baby?
Laughs?
One?
First?
When a baby laughs for the first time,
that's when a fairy is born.
Incredible.
Lizzy, that's only the beginning.
Guess I always knew
This could all come true
Still it feels so new
Being here with you
Can't believe my eyes
A new world comes alive
Spring and summer
Love and laughter
We'll live happy ever after
We'll shine brighter
Than we thought we'd be
Because you showed me
How to believe
More than just pretend
I'll make believe again
I hope this never ends
Maybe we'll be friends
Now everything I know
Everything I know
I'll never let it go
Never let it go
Spring and summer
Love and laughter
We'll live happy ever after
We'll shine brighter
Than we thought we'd be
Because you showed me
How to believe
Okay, everybody, listen up.
This road should take us straight
to the human house.
So how far is it from the road
to the house, do you think?
Not that far, really.
The only question is, how flooded is it?
That's a good point.
Well, I'm gonna remain optimistic.
- We'll get to Tink in no time.
- I'm with you, Sil.
We're almost there.
Why, look,
we're picking up speed already.
Did you feel that? We're moving faster.
Hey, guys!
We're heading right for a waterfall!
Great polliwogs!
We have to make the turn!
Ease the sheets and get ready to jibe!
- What?
Ease the sheet and get ready to jibe!
- What did he say?
Loosen the ropes and turn the sail!
- Oh, no!
- Look out!
Man overboard!
Hard to port! Hard to port!
Turn the boat! Turn the boat!
Guys! We're running out of river!
That's all right,
'cause all we need's a little.
- Rosetta, come grab my feet.
- What?
Hang on! We're going straight down!
Oh, no!
Brace yourselves!
- Who's alive?
- Not me.
Me, either. I can't find a pulse!
It's not there!
I'm telling you, I don't... I'm good.
Sorry!
Looks like we're walking from here.
- But... Walking where?
- We could be anywhere.
Everything looks the same
from down here.
And there's no way of knowing
which way to go.
Clank! Where did you find that?
I don't know. Here on the ground.
Is it yours?
I know where we are.
Tinker Bell, this is so fascinating.
Thank you.
I had no idea fairies were responsible
for changing the seasons.
I thought it had something to do
with the Earth's axis
- as it rotated around the sun.
- That's what we wanted you to think.
Well, I think we've covered everything.
I hope Father's impressed.
And now, for the finale.
The whole fairy land, Pixie Hollow.
It worked!
Tinker Bell, I can't wait to show Father.
Tinker Bell? Are you all right?
Tinker Bell?
Sorry. Yeah, let's go show your dad.
Looks like the rain has let up some.
You might be able to make it home
to your friends now.
Maybe this could help you.
Yes.
Such a clever tinker.
Take care of yourself.
I'll never forget you, Tinker Bell.
You'd best hurry. The break
in the weather may not last long.
Good bye.
And I'll never forget you, Lizzy.
- Father, look!
- Not just now, Lizzy.
My hands are rather full at the moment.
I made it especially for you, Father.
It's just like your field journal.
- It's filled with lots of facts.
- Yes, yes, that sounds wonderful,
but I'm in the middle
of a potential catastrophe here.
I can't look at it now.
- But Father, it's a field journal, and I...
- I don't have time.
I have to find some way
to deal with all these leaks
before they destroy my work.
- When will you be able to look at it?
- I don't know. Maybe later.
You always say that.
Tinker Bell!
You came back! I'm so glad to see you.
Tinker Bell, Father has no time
for the field journal.
I think I can fix that.
Vidia, you sure you know
where you're going?
Yes. Tinker Bell and I walked by here.
I just have to find the road.
Road? What road?
That road!
That's not a road. That's a muddy river.
So, I guess we need to find a bridge.
Or be spontaneous and jump right in.
It's not deep. We can walk across.
Yeah, no. I don't really do mud.
- But you're a garden fairy!
- Ironic, isn't it?
- Rosetta!
Okay, all right. I'm coming.
It's squishy. What was that?
She's stuck!
I can get myself out of here.
All right, all right.
Someone just get me something
to grab onto.
- Got it! Clanky, rescue device.
- Right, Bobble. You can count on us!
Okay. Let's give this a try.
Do you feel that?
She's starting to break free.
I don't think so.
- Come on, hurry!
- Pull! Pull!
Pull!
Hello? Is somebody out there?
Anyone?
- Grab this! Hurry!
- Are you kidding me?
Trust me. And hold on tight.
Oh, Well.
We got the...
- ... rescue device.
- You scared the petals right off of me!
Did we miss anything?
"My, what a splendid tea service.
I am really quite impressed. "
Then I say,
"Why, thank you, Tinker Bell.
"You are too kind. "
You hold your pinkie out, like this,
and that's the way
you throw a proper tea party.
Good night, Lizzy.
There we...
I'm going to bed.
There just aren't enough hours
in the day.
Good morning, Tinker Bell.
How did you sleep last night?
Well, I... Actually, I didn't,
but that doesn't matter.
You should go downstairs
to your father.
- Lizzy?
- Yes, Father?
Good morning, my dear.
All the leaks seem to have stopped.
I just wanted to make sure
everything is okay in here.
Yes. Just fine. No leaks at all. So...
Strange. It's as if
they mended themselves.
It's still raining outside.
I can't imagine how on Earth
such a thing could occur.
Well, there must be an explanation
that I'm just not thinking of.
Well, I'm sure you'll think of it, Father.
- Off we go.
- Perhaps down in your study.
You always do your best thinking there.
I wish you luck.
- Okay, well, play nicely.
- Yes, of course. Bye, Father.
That was close.
What are you doing?
This is your chance.
Is that why you fixed those leaks?
So he can spend more time with me?
I've really been wanting
to show him this.
Okay, okay. I'll go.
Father, since you have more time,
maybe I can show you
my scientific research.
- The butterfly. It's gone!
- What?
The apatura iris
with the irregular wing pattern.
I was going to present it
to the museum tonight.
This was my big opportunity,
and now it's gone.
- Elizabeth, did you release it?
- No.
Well, I didn't do it.
And since there is no one else
in the house,
there is only one logical explanation.
- It must have been you.
- I didn't do it, Father.
I'm going to give you one more chance.
Tell me the truth.
I could tell you, Father,
but you wouldn't believe me.
Very well. Off to your room, young lady.
I'm very disappointed in you.
You know, I was just thinking,
if Tink were here,
- how not quiet it would be right now.
- You can say that again.
Okay, okay, okay. Who am I?
That's the exact shade!
Quite a bit of spirit
in that little tinker, eh?
That's for sure. In fact,
I still can't believe she got captured.
Yeah. It's very unlike Tink
to be caught with her guard down.
- I wonder what really happened.
- Well, we'll find out soon.
Yep. With every step we take we come
closer and closer to Tinker Bell.
She'll tell us what happened.
Listen, there's something
you all should know.
Tinker Bell getting trapped
is all my fault!
I slammed that door on Tinker Bell,
to teach her a lesson.
I tried to get her out,
but the door was stuck.
I tried, but I couldn't, and now
I've put her and all of us in danger.
I am so sorry.
Honey, this is not your fault.
We all know that Tink can get
into plenty of trouble all by herself.
It scares me to think what would have
happened if you weren't there, Vidia.
I don't know what to say.
- How about faith...
- Trust...
- And...
And pixie dust.
- And pixie dust!
Can you reach it, Clanky?
- Almost. Just a little more.
- Here, let me.
Okay. Now, can you see anything?
No! There's a big building in the way.
Building. It's a house. That's it!
Clanky! We've got it!
- What've we got?
- House! Get off.
- I'm sorry.
- I can't feel my legs.
It doesn't matter what I say.
He never believes me.
I'm so sorry, Lizzy.
I'm so glad you're here.
You're my best friend.
I wish I were a fairy, just like you.
Then I could help the flowers bloom
and talk to animals
and fly around with the other fairies
all the time.
That would be fun.
Where are we going?
What is going on up there?
I was going to present it
to the museum tonight.
Now the butterfly is gone.
Oh, my! I'm... I'm flying!
Look at me! I'm a fairy!
All clear!
- Sorry.
- Careful.
- That's my ear.
- Sorry.
- That's the nose. Careful.
- Can't see!
Okay. Tinker Bell is upstairs.
The little girl has her in a cage.
In a cage?
And there's also a large human
in the house
who doesn't like creatures with wings.
He pins them up in display cases.
- Great. Anything else?
- Yes. The cat.
Cat! What cat?
- That cat!
Fawn, you're an animal fairy.
What are we supposed to do?
- Fawn?
- Fly!
- Our wings are wet.
- And who knows when they'll be dry.
Okay, okay. Run!
- Clank!
- Come on!
- I'm okay.
We still need to get to that stairwell.
Any ideas?
If we could just build a bridge
or something.
- That's it. A bridge!
- Guys? Guys?
- A bridge made out of what?
- Guys!
Clank! You're a genius!
It was nothing.
All right. Let's do this.
- We need some more plates!
- Okay. Start passing them up, Clanky.
Aye, aye! Here they come!
Get ready for more. Hello!
We've got a full plate back here!
No, no, no. No. No, please.
Get back!
Rosetta! Is this what I think it is?
That is exactly
what you think it is. Catnip!
You get to Tink
and we'll take care of the cat!
Got it!
- Lizzy?
- Coming, Father!
- Why, hello, Father. May I help you?
- What's going on in here?
- Nothing.
Nothing? Sounds like a herd of
elephants have been marching up here.
Look at this room.
It looks like a cyclone hit it.
- It's not that bad.
- Not that bad?
Your books are all over the floor,
your toys are everywhere
and you tore your curtains. What?
How did you get footprints
on the ceiling?
This is simply too much.
A temper tantrum of this magnitude
is unacceptable.
But I wasn't having a tantrum!
Then how did this happen?
And the truth this time.
If I tell you the truth,
you still won't believe me.
Elizabeth, the truth.
I was flying. My fairy showed me how.
For goodness sake.
Your make-believe fairy did this?
You've got to stop this nonsense!
But it's not nonsense, Father.
It's the truth!
You have a real fairy
living in your room?
Yes! And I can prove it.
Just look at the research we did.
Elizabeth. This is what
you've been doing?
Field journals are to be filled with fact,
not fairy tales.
But Father, these are facts!
I don't understand this foolishness,
Lizzy. You have such talent.
- Why would you waste it this way?
- Why can't you just believe me?
I believe in what is real,
and it's about time
you started doing the same.
Father, wait!
I know this is difficult for you
to understand,
but this is all make-believe.
- No! They're real!
- Elizabeth, this discussion is over.
But Father!
It... It...
See? I told you. Fairies are real!
It's okay. She won't hurt you.
It's... Well, it's extraordinary!
Aren't her wings beautiful?
Yes. Very similar to Apoidea.
Or, no, no, odonata.
Look at the limb proportionality
to the cranial radius.
- Fascinating!
- Isn't she magical?
She's some sort
of evolutionary mutation.
She's not a bug, she's a person.
- Exactly!
- Tinker Bell!
This is going to be
the discovery of the century!
Tink, watch out!
- Vidia?
- Get out of the way!
I must get this to the museum
right away!
Father, no!
Please, Father! Wait!
- You can't do this!
- Lizzy, I don't have much time.
The trustees will only wait for me
until 9:00.
Please, go back in the house.
Don't worry.
Mrs. Perkins will be here any second.
Tinker Bell, I'm so sorry!
My father's taking your friend
to the city!
- Step, step, Step-
- Tinker Bell?
- Tinker Bell!
Look, it's your friends.
- Hurry.
- That's it. Good kitty.
Look, Lizzy's father trapped Vidia
in a jar while she was saving me.
- We have to hurry and rescue her.
- Here we go again!
- How are we gonna get there?
- Yeah, it's still raining.
Maybe we can't fly in the rain,
but I think I know someone who can.
I'm scared, Tinker Bell.
Floating around my room is one thing,
but flying all the way to London...
That easy, huh?
Okay. I'll be brave.
All right, fairies.
We need all the pixie dust we can get.
This girl's got a long journey
ahead of her.
All aboard!
Ready?
This better work.
Sorry, fairies.
Careful now!
Hi, Mrs. Perkins. Bye, Mrs. Perkins.
Bye, dear. Fly back soon.
Good idea.
Sorry!
Out of the way!
There he is!
Tinker Bell, I can't keep up.
He's going too fast.
Tink! Tinker Bell, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no! Come on!
Come on, please, let them still be there.
- Father!
- What in the world?
Father, stop! Don't take her in there!
It... it... it... It can't be.
Lizzy? You're flying.
Yes, I am.
But how? How are you doing that?
My friends showed me how.
I... I don't understand.
You don't have to understand.
You just have to believe.
I do believe.
I do believe!
Father!
Lizzy, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
I'll never doubt you again.
Vidia!
- Let's go home, Father.
- But how?
Think happy thoughts.
- Lift your arms and kick your feet!
- Careful!
I think I'm getting the hang of it. Yes!
Why, I'm flying!
- You're doing it, Father! You're doing it!
- I could get used to this! Just a second.
There's something
I've always wanted to do. Follow me!
- Hey, Tink.
- Hey, Vidia.
So, you ever been
to one of these before?
Yeah. It's pretty fun.
- What are you supposed to do?
- It's easy. You just pick this up.
- Like this?
- Yeah. And then you hold it out.
- Got it!
- Now, just raise your pinkie, like this.
And then you say, "Excuse me, miss,
but may I have a spot of tea?"
Why, certainly, Miss Bell.
A nice, fresh cup.
But of course you may have one, too.
This is a tea party, after all.
How about a cup for me, Miss Griffiths?
Why, of course, Doctor.
- It's my pleasure, I'm sure.
- Thank you.
- And would you like one lump or two?
- Make mine three.
Father!
Thank you.
- Isn't this pleasant, Father?
- I can't imagine anything better.
Although, chiming the Big Ben
comes a close second.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Scrumptious.
Don't even think about it.
So, where were we? Yes.
"Fairies have many magical talents.
They can talk to animals,
"make the flowers bloom,
create warm summer breezes. "
Lizzy, what a beautiful drawing.
"And some invent
the most clever little gadgets. "
Well, Tink,
you found something to fix after all.
Yeah. I guess I did.
"They bring the change of seasons,
and help nature in many ways.
"But the best talent a fairy can have
is simply being a friend. "
The breezes blow the clouds away
A million things I want to say
I don't ever want this day
To be done
Summer's just begun
Never seen the sky so blue
Everything is clear and new
Happy just to be with you in the sun
Summer's just begun
Hold my hand and fly
Never say goodbye
Cross the open sky
Leave the world behind
I will be all right
If you stay by my side
Spring and summer
Love and laughter
We'll live happy ever after
We'll fly higher
Than we thought we'd be
Because you showed me
How to believe
Tiny shining star
I know who you are
You're never very far
We'll never be apart
Sparkle in my eye
Light the sky tonight
Spring and summer
Love and laughter
We'll live happy ever after
We'll fly higher
Than we thought we'd be
Because you showed me
How to believe
In me
Fall and winter
Love and laughter
We'll live happy ever after
We'll fly higher
Than we thought we'd be
Because you showed me
How to believe
Yeah
Hold my hand and fly
Never say goodbye